王牌特工2
黄金圈
艾格西
Eggy.
你介意和我坐一辆车吗
You mind if I share your cab?
查理·赫斯基斯                     档案号：SB-851001
受拒的王牌特工申请者              年龄：26岁          体重：73.4公斤
.                             身高：1.82米        瞳色：蓝色
.                                                 发色：棕色
查理
Charlie?
还真是讽刺  不是吗
It's ironic, isn't it?
你穿着考究  我却衣装平平
You look like a gentleman, I look like a pleb.
如果我是你  我就会打开车门
If I was you, I'd unlock your cab.
皮特  带我们离开这里
Pete, get us out of here!
你觉得那玩意这次能管用吗
You think that shit's gonna work this time?
你太不自量力了
You're way out of your depth.
该死
Fuck!
漂移模式
干掉他
Take him out!
梅林  紫色警报
Merlin! We've got a Code Purple.
我的司机阵亡了
My driver's down.
请求炸飞那些混账
Permission to blow these fuckers away.
否决
Denied.
无法控制
Cannot be contained.
向南边去  我来疏通路径
Head south, I'm clearing the route.
该死
Shit!
梅林  正在进入海德公园
Merlin, I'm entering Hyde Park.
我可以开火了吗
Can I get on with it?
梅林
Merlin!
暗区确认  允许开火
Dark zone confirmed. Permission to fire.
终于可以了
Oh, thank fuck for that!
没时间放松了  警方就跟在你们后面
No time to relax. Police are right behind you.
.                         加拉哈德
海德公园
在他们赶到你们的位置之前你们有30秒时间
You have 30 seconds before they reach your position.
直接前往天鹅汇合点
Go directly to Rendezvous Swan.
梅林  你知道我现在没有挡风玻璃吧
Merlin, you do realize I haven't even got a windscreen right now?
我记得你在训练的时候
I seem to remember from your training
你相当擅长憋气
you were rather good at holding your breath.
这不是次复仇任务
It wasn't a revenge mission.
查理本可以当即杀掉你的
Charlie could've just killed you immediately.
不是自夸  但是通过我的训练
Not boasting, but I trained him well enough
即使是他也不会把这件事搞砸
that even he wouldn't mess that up.
梅林  我很抱歉
Merlin, I'm sorry,
我们得等到明天再听取简报了
we're gonna have to do the debrief tomorrow.
我今天晚上有约
I've got to get to a dinner tonight...
如果我错过了  我还
and if I miss it, let's just say
不如就让查理杀了我
Charlie might as well have killed me.
如果你等不及
Well, if you can't wait
警方对公园的现场进行清理
for the police to clear the park...
在角落里还有另一个出口
there's another way out in the corner.
出口
该死
Fuck!
那次晚餐有多重要
How important is that dinner?
我就让你看看
Let me show you.
使用者
加拉哈德
密码
准许进入
真要命
For fuck's sake!
宝贝
Babe.
我回家了
I'm home!
我在这里
I'm here.
究竟出了什么事
What the hell happened?
说来话长你得先吻我
It's a long story that deserves a kiss.
JB都不会亲你
Not even JB would kiss you right now.
如果你真的爱我  就亲我一口
If you really love me, just one little kiss.
你真的打算亲吗
You were really gonna do it?
是的
Yeah.
真是真情流露
Now, that is true love right there.
太棒了  我去换衣服
Amazing. I'm gonna go get changed.
♪ 生日快乐♪
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
蒂尔达亲手给你做的  兄弟
And Tilde made that for you herself, bruv.
皇家烘焙师不上班吗
The royal baker's not available.
闭嘴吧  布兰登
Oh, shut up, Brandon.
尤其是如果你想要常常这个的话
Especially if you want some of this.
等等  那瓶是不是那个瑞典货
Oh! Wait. Is that that Swedish stuff right there?
没错
Yes.
不  不  我可一滴都不要碰
No, no. I ain't drinkin' none of that.
上次在这的时候我喝得神志不清
Last time here, I was wrecked, man.
但那是因为你酒量不行  贾马尔
Yeah, but that's 'cause you were a lightweight, Jamal.
不  不  宝贝  我就不用了  谢谢你
No, no, babe, I'm good. Not for me, thank you.
什么  怎么回事  兄弟
Oh, what? What's going on, man?
明晚我要第一次
I'm meeting her parents
去见她的父母
for the first time tomorrow night.
我想要留下个好印象  - 那又怎样
I wanna make a good impression, - so what?
对了  贾马尔  你可以在明晚我们出去的时候
Oh, yeah, Jamal, are you free to dogsit JB
负责照顾JB
tomorrow night while we're there?
抱歉  兄弟  我明天要照顾我奶奶
Ah, sorry, bruv, I've got to look after my nan tomorrow.
不过   利亚姆有空
But Liam's free, though.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
我不行  伙计  我对狗过敏
I can't, mate. I'm allergic to dogs.
扯淡
Bullshit.
实际上是对照顾狗屎过敏
Dogshit, actually.
那就只剩下你了  布兰登  你明晚有什么打算
That leaves you, Brandon. What you doing tomorrow night?
好吧  我来找看你的狗  伙计
Yeah, I'll look after your dog, mate,
但是我有一个条件
but I got one condition.
什么条件
What's that?
- 你得和我们一起喝  - 没错
- You have a drink with us. - Yeah.
恭谨不如从命  宝贝
Got to do it, babe.
来吧
Got to do it.
布兰登  生日快乐
Brandon, happy birthday!
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
- 太好了 - 干杯
- Yeah. - Cheers.
该死
Shit.
我的毒品到处都是
My drugs are everywhere.
我从来都不对它们感兴趣
They were never my thing...
但是我却走到了这一步
but here I am,
运营着着世界上最大的贩毒集团
running the biggest drug cartel in the world.
唯一的缺点就是必须得住在这荒无人烟的地方
The only downside is having to live in the middle of nowhere.
严格来说  这片遗迹还没有被发现
You know, these ruins are technically undiscovered.
我不过是增加一点小修饰让我能记起家乡
I just added a few touches to remind me of home.
我生长对50年代的怀旧中
I grew up on all that awesome 50s nostalgia.
《油脂》《美国风情画》《快乐时光》
Grease. American Graffiti. Happy Days.
《油脂》（grease）该片讲述的是在美国Rydell 高中，10位青年人如何纠缠于复杂的爱情关系，从而表达青春期的焦虑烦恼的故事《美国风情画》(American Graffiti)描述一群刚步出高中校园，即将因不同的人生选择各自发展的哥儿们，在小城一夜之间的经历。故事
发生在60年代初加州的一个小镇上《快乐时光》（Happy Days）是1974年～1984年由ABC电视网在美国放映的一部系列情景喜剧。它向我们展示了美国20世纪50年
代晚期到60年代早期的快乐生活
但是我叛离了那条道路
But I digress.
你需要理解的是
The thing you need to understand
辛劳与智谋是
is the hard work and ingenuity...
达成对全球毒品市场垄断的
it took to achieve a global monopoly...
不可或缺的元素
on the drug trade.
而我二者兼备  不是我要自吹自擂
And that's all on me. Not to toot my own horn...
我只是觉得让新成员了解
I just think it's really important
黄金圈的历史
for new recruits to understand...
很有必要
the history of The Golden Circle.
你们是故交  是吗
So. Lifelong friends, huh?
查尔斯  你觉得你的哥们
Charles, do you think your buddy here
值得加入我们吗
is worthy of joining us?
罂粟女士  如果我不这么认为
Ms. Poppy, I would not have brought him
我就不会这么大老远把他带来了
all the way to see you if I didn't think so.
太好了  你们饿了吗
Excellent. Well, you hungry?
饥肠辘辘
Starving.
太好了  这边请
Wonderful! Right this way.
别拘束
Make yourselves at home.
那么  伙伴们
So, fellas...
我有一些事情需要说明
I have a couple of things that I wanna clarify.
你们知道在黄金圈内
You understand that in The Golden Circle...
我的权威不容置疑吧
my authority is never to be questioned, right?
好友遵循指令的重要性
And the importance of following orders?
你们明白吗
Do you understand that?
忠诚的价值
And the value of loyalty?
点头很简单  不是吗
It's easy to nod, isn't it?
我不喜欢简单  我想要证据
I don't like easy. I like proof.
- 你叫什么名字  - 安格尔  女士
- What's your name? - Angel, ma'am.
安格尔  宝贝儿
Angel, baby.
嘿
Hey.
你的老伙计  查尔斯  搞砸了
Your old pal, Charles, has messed up.
我就告诉你这么多
That's all I'm gonna tell you,
因为你只需要知道这么多
'cause that's all you need to know.
把他放到绞肉机里  好吗
So put him in the mincer, okay?
本尼
软件版本1.0.2
不  罂粟女士
No, Miss Poppy!
干得好
Good job!
看到街对面我的沙龙了吗
See my salon across the way?
到那去给你的形象做个改造
Head there for your makeover.
艾格西  希望你有胃口
Eggsy, I hope you're hungry.
宝贝  我要带份早餐上班的时候吃
Oh, babe, I was gonna grab breakfast at work.
那看起来很精致  但是我要迟到了
This looks lovely, but I'm running late.
我觉得我们可以练习一下
I just thought maybe we could practice?
为了今晚
For tonight.
练习
Practice?
吃饭吗
Eating?
你说你从来没在王宫吃过饭
You said you've never eaten at a palace before.
而且爸爸对餐桌礼仪又很挑剔
And Pappa is sort of picky about table manners.
正巧  我对这些繁文缛节一清二楚
Well, as it happens, babe, I've got this shit on lock.
我知道每一把叉子
I know what every single one
和刀子的用途
of them knives and forks is for.
这是黄油刀
This is a butter knife.
这是唯一一个你需要特别记住的
It's the only one you need to remember,
其它的餐具就很简单了
the rest of the cutlery is easy.
你从最外侧开始
You start from the outside,
随着餐品的变化使用内侧的餐具
and you work your way in with each course.
别让人把你描述成执刀如笔
And never let anyone describe you as "H.K.L.P."...
那是什么意思
What's that?
像握笔一样握刀
"Holds knife like pen."
一个被错误的认为
A habit erroneously believed
是上层阶级的餐桌礼仪的习惯
to be upper class dining etiquette.
其实正好相反
It is quite the opposite.
白葡萄酒  甜品酒  红葡萄酒  水还有汽水
White wine, pudding wine, red wine, water and pop.
或者其它你喜欢的烈酒
Or whatever tipple takes your fancy.
我要等其他人的餐点都上了
Am I supposed to wait for everyone else
之后才能开始用餐吗
to be served before I start eating?
只有在上的餐品是冷餐的时候才需要
Only if the dish being served is cold.
或者有女王  其他情况可以放开吃
Or if the Queen is present. Otherwise tuck in.
说实话
Got to be honest...
从来没想过和王室相关的部分能用得上
never really thought the royalty bit would be relevant.
哈利会很得意的
Harry would've been chuffed.
我真希望我能见到他
Oh. I wish I could've met him.
你也想他了  不是吗  腌黄瓜先生
You miss him too, don't you, Mr. Pickle?
腌黄瓜先生说是
Mr. Pickle says, "Yeah."
不  不  不用起身了  我没事
Hey, no, no, sit down, I'm fine.
我没事  祝你今天愉快
I'm fine. Have a good day.
好的
Okay.
裁缝街 西1
威斯敏斯特市
加拉哈德  你迟到了
Ah, Galahad! You're late.
我们还担心
We were wondering if you'd had
你又碰到查理了
a second encounter with Charlie.
我倒希望如此  我很期待能够解决他
I wish. I'm looking forward to finishing him off.
好了  先生们
All right, gents.
梅林  请进
Merlin, come in.
加拉哈德和兰斯洛特
Galahad and Lancelot,
留下来听取梅林的简报
please remain for Merlin's debrief.
其他人  在19：00再会
Everyone else, reconvene at 1900 hours.
那么
So...
在出租车里袭击加拉哈德的人
the man who attacked Galahad in the taxi
查理·赫斯基斯
档案号：SB-851001
年龄：26岁
体重：73.4公斤
身高：1.82米
瞳色：蓝色
发色：棕色
是查理·赫斯基
was Charlie Hesketh.
一名变节的受拒申请者
Rejected Kingsman applicant turned bad.
我们最后一次见到他是在里士满·瓦伦丁的总部
We last saw him back at Richmond Valentine's HQ.
我抓住了个该死的间谍
I've caught a fucking spy!
闭路电视-信号
地点：瓦伦丁
像其他人一样
Like everyone else there...
查理的颈部有植入安全芯片
Charlie had a security implant in his neck.
我们不得已利用了这个弱点
A weakness we had no choice but to exploit.
梅林  壮丽宏伟  不是吗
Hey, Merlin. Still fucking spectacular, eh?
别这样  大伙  放松点  我们拯救了世界
Come on, guys, loosen up. We saved the world.
没错
Yeah.
不幸的是  加拉哈德  你同样救了查理
Unfortunately, Galahad, you also saved Charlie.
在你把他电晕的同时  破坏了他的植入物
When you electrocuted him, you damaged his implant.
他只失去了一只胳膊
Instead of his head exploding...
和声带  而没有爆炸
he only lost an arm and his vocal chords.
那个混账应该谢谢我
Fucker should be thanking me.
现在他要来复仇吗
And now he's back for revenge?
我们不这么认为  先生
We don't think so, sir.
我们认为他被招募进了
We believe he's being recruited
某个不知名的组织
by an unknown organization.
兰斯洛特
Lancelot?
得到了警方
Got the police autopsy reports
对查理越野车中的同事的尸检报告
from Charlie's colleagues in the SUVs.
他们不止是雇佣杀手
They're not just goons for hire.
指纹被移除
Fingerprints removed.
牙齿被磨平
Teeth filed smooth.
我进行了面部识别  一无所获
I did a face recognition. Nothing.
那个东西呢
And that thing?
一个由24克拉黄金制成的装饰性纹身
A cosmetic tattoo made of 24-carat gold.
他们身上都有
They all had them.
我们似乎是在应对某种秘密组织
Seems like we're looking at some kind of underworld organization.
罂粟夫人送我来进行改造
Senora Poppy has sent me for my makeover.
跟我来
Follow me.
请脱下你的衬衫
Please take your shirt off.
真是漂亮  不是吗
It's beautiful, isn't it?
不是那个
Not that.
是这个
This.
♪旭日高悬天空湛蓝♪
♪ The sun is out The sky is blue ♪
用餐愉快
Bon appetit.
♪ 没有云朵毁坏这美景♪
♪ There's not a cloud To spoil the view ♪
♪但是下起了雨♪
♪ But it's raining ♪
♪落进了我的心房♪
♪ Raining in my heart ♪
♪悲伤啊  悲伤♪
♪ Oh, misery, misery ♪
♪我会遇到什么样的邂逅♪
♪ What's gonna become of me? ♪
怎么样
How is it?
很美味
It's delicious.
欢迎加入黄金圈
Welcome to Golden Circle.
♪落进我的心房♪
♪ Raining in my heart ♪
瑞典
为了方便你
I think we should do you the favor
我想我们就用英语进行对话吧
of conversing in English, yes.
那么  跟我说说
So, tell me...
你是做什么的
what do you do?
我为皇家绅士工作  是裁缝  殿下
I work for Kingsman, the tailors, Your Highness.
你可以称我的女儿为殿下
You may address my daughter as "Your Highness."
请用陛下来称呼王后和我本人
Please address the Queen and myself with "Your Majesty."
爸爸  这是顿家宴
Pappa, this is a family dinner...
不是国事活动
not some state function.
好吧  艾格西
Well then, Eggsy.
你对于目前印度金融市场的
What do you make of the current situation
现状有什么看法
in the Indian financial markets?
爸爸
Pappa!
呃
Uh...
我认为我们不能低估欧洲央行
I don't think we can underestimate the impact
量化宽松措施造成的冲击
of ECB's quantitative easing measures.
当然  美国联邦储备金率的
And of course, the liquidity wave
上调导致的流动性浪潮
from the US Federal Reserve rate hike...
遭到了抑制
getting pushed back.
弗里达·卡洛
Frida Kahlo.
弗里达·卡罗（Frida Kahlo 1907年7月6日－1954年7月13日）是一位知名的墨西哥女画家。弗里达的本名是MagdalenaCarmenFriedaKahloyCalderón，
她出生在墨西哥城南部的科瑶坎（Coyoacan）街区。父亲是德裔犹太画家与摄影师，家族来自罗马尼亚的欧拉地Oradea（二战
前是匈牙利属地）。
除了1939年她的一幅画作被卢浮宫所收藏
Well, other than the 1939 acquisition by the Louvre...
她在上世纪70年代的
she wasn't really acknowledged
墨西哥艺术运动之前
until the new Mexicanisimo art movement...
都一直没有被真正被认可
of the late 1970s.
摩尔复兴建筑
Moorish revival.
萨米扎诺宫
Ah. The Palazzo Sammezzano.
在托斯卡尼
In Tuscany.
美轮美奂
Beautiful.
蓝牙技术
Bluetooth technology.
当然  得名于
Which, of course, got its name
传奇的丹麦国王
from the legendary Danish king...
哈拉尔德·布拉塔德  他的姓
Harald Blatand, whose name
翻译为英文即为蓝牙
translates to "Bluetooth" in English.
哈拉尔蓝牙王 Harald Blatand，丹麦国王（940—986年在位），哈拉尔征服了整个丹麦和挪威，并使丹麦人成为基督教徒——“耶林石”
上记载的哈拉尔蓝牙王的功绩，哈拉尔国王下令为纪念父亲高姆和母亲翠拉而立此碑。
蓝牙的标志是他的
And the Bluetooth logo is his initials
古诺斯语如尼文的人名首字母
in Norse runic symbols.
相信你您也知道
And, as I'm sure you know...
蓝牙的标志是他姓名首字母
the Bluetooth logo is his initials...
在古诺斯如尼符号的缩写
in Norse runic symbols.
天呐  艾格西
Oh, my God, Eggsy.
他怎么就是不吃他的布丁
Why isn't he eating his fucking pudding?
我需要研究他的黄金纹身
I need to research this gold tattoo.
我找到了其它
I found records of other people
进行了相同身体改造的人
with the same body modifications.
他们所有人与之都有
All of them have high level involvement...
国际毒品贩运有深层联系
with crime and international drug trafficking.
还有关于叫做黄金圈的东西的传闻
And there's rumors of something called The Golden Circle.
发送消息
你
是
最
大
b
加拉哈德
你是最棒的
最棒的特工还是最棒的朋友
Best agent or best friend?
都有 (*^_^*)
别这样  JB  消停一会儿  伙计
Come on, JB. Give it a rest, mate.
别再抓门了  我要被责怪了
Stop scratching the door. I'm gonna get the blame now.
进去吧  满意了吧
There you are. Happy?
太阳报   太阳报    太阳报
香肠危害 埃尔顿·约翰  平手
还有个唱机台子
With the decks and all that.
我去
Shit, boy!
什么
What the...
你觉得怎么样  JB
Do you reckon, JB...
我有当模特的潜质吗
model material?
我必须得说  我没想到你这么博学
I must say, you're really not as I expected.
感谢您的褒奖
Well, thank you very much...
陛下
Your Majesty.
艾格西  是你吗  伙计
Eggsy? Is that you, mate?
这是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on here?
你是什么帮派成员吗
You a gangster now or something?
活见鬼了  那是蒂尔德爸妈的家吗
Fuckin' hell. Is that Tilde's mom and dad's house?
跟你说  不管你是做什么的  加我一个
Tell you what. Whatever you're doing, I want in.
放下
Put it down!
为什么
Why?
我说了  马上给我放下来
I said, put it down now!
出什么问题了
What's wrong with it?
关掉  快点关掉
Shut it! Fucking shut it!
艾格西  你说什么
Eggsy. I beg your pardon?
关掉  快关掉
Shut it! Shut it now!
好了 伙计  别紧张
All right, mate. Chill your boots.
艾格西  怎么
Eggsy, what...
哦  不  我的天哪  不  我很抱歉
Oh, no. Oh, my God, no. I'm so sorry.
你闭嘴  你给我惹了够多麻烦了
You shut up and all. You got me in enough trouble.
十之二目标摧毁
下一事项
The next order of business...
珀西瓦尔特工
Agent Percival.
会议
亚瑟
Arthur.
导弹来袭
哦妈的
Oh, fuck.
目标全部摧毁
好了
Yep.
王牌特工变成烤面饼了
Kingsman is crumpets.
有点像吐司  但是是英国版的
Like toast, but British.
为了对你表达感激
And to say thank you...
我给你准备了礼物  查理
I got you a present, Charlie.
我的手下给你做了这个
My guys made you this.
更大  更强  更棒  我叫它
Bigger, badder, better. I call it...
末日手臂
ARMageddon.
来看看你的能耐有没有提升
Let's see if your game improves.
哦哟
Ouch.
有人炸平了王牌特工
Someone decides to wipe out
所有的地产
every Kingsman property...
所有的特工  然而不知什么原因
every agent, and somehow...
你恰好不在家
conveniently, you weren't at home.
我也可以对你说同样的话
I could say the same thing about you.
什么  你觉得我会杀死罗克茜
What, you think I'd kill Roxy?
还有我的朋友  布兰登  还有我的狗
And my mate, Brandon, and my fucking dog?
不会
No.
你觉得我会
You think I would?
这个东西
This thing...
黑了我们
hacked us.
显然  这个胳膊可以远程控制
Clearly, this arm can be remotely controlled.
我还活着  唯一的原因是我的地址
I'm only alive because my address
没有在特工的数据库里
wasn't on the database with the agents.
和查理合作的人
Whoever Charlie's working with
觉得小小员工值不上一个导弹
doesn't think that mere staff are missile-worthy.
这不好笑
This ain't funny.
罗克茜死了
Roxy is dead!
所有人都死了  没了  你毫不在乎吗
Everyone's dead! Gone! Do you even care?
你给我打起精神来
Pull yourself together.
想想你的训练
Remember your training.
在这个情景下没有宣泄感情的时间
There's no time for emotion in this scenario.
好了
Now...
既然所有存活的特工都已到场
as all surviving agents are present,
我们遵循末日协议
we follow the doomsday protocol.
等这个完成后  也只有在这以后
When that's done, and only then...
你才可以在私下落泪
you may shed a tear in private.
好
Okay.
末日协议是什么
What's the doomsday protocol?
我们去购物
We go shopping.
我们是皇家绅士的人  我们想买酒
We're from Kingsman. We'd like to buy some wine.
用三号品酒室  谢谢
And use tasting room number three, please.
我的前辈们没有一个
Not one of my predecessors
曾处在这种局面过
has ever been in this situation before.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
啊哈
A-ha.
记得这个吧
Remember this?
我怎么可能忘记
Yeah, how could I forget?
在这个保险箱里的东西是我们所有麻烦的答案
Whatever's in that safe is the answer to all our problems.
联邦英雄
肯塔基纯波本
威士忌
就这个
Is that it?
我猜这应该是什么上流社会的幽默
I suppose that must be upper-class humor.
我不懂
I don't get it.
我也不懂  我们他妈现在干什么啊
Me neither. What the fuck are we supposed to do now?
我觉得我们应该喝一杯
I think we should drink a toast
敬我们陨落的同志们
to our fallen comrades.
敬罗克茜
To Roxy.
罗克茜
Roxy.
哦
Ooh.
- 敬亚瑟  - 亚瑟
- To Arthur. - Arthur.
嗯
Mmm.
我们要不要也敬JB一杯
Should we do one for JB?
我觉得要
I think we should.
我应该预料到的
I should have seen it coming.
查理  出租车
Charlie, the taxi.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
扯淡  梅林  不都是你的错
No, that's bullshit, Merlin. It ain't all your fault.
你是最棒的  老哥
You're the best, bruv.
真的  没有你
Honestly, without you...
我很久以前就要迷失了
I'd have lost it a long time ago.
我觉得我们需要敬苏格兰一杯
I think we should drink to Scotland.
说真的  我觉得我们应该喝得差不多了
I think we've probably had enough, to be honest.
你说的应该没错
You're probably right.
肯塔基酿造
- 梅林  - 哎
- Merlin. - Aye?
我觉得我们要去一趟肯塔基
I think we're going to Kentucky.
肯德基
Fried Chicken?
我喜欢肯德基
I love fried chicken.
不  真的肯塔基  看
No, proper Kentucky. Look.
你知道我还喜欢什么吗
You know what else I love?
西部乡村音乐
Country and western music.
♪乡村的路♪
♪ Country roads ♪
♪带我回家♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪回到我的归宿♪
♪ To the place I belong ♪
联邦英雄
肯塔基州  美国
哦  我们把酒桶放在这里陈化
Oh! Here's where we leave the casks to age.
很不幸的是我们不能进去
Unfortunately, we can't go in,
因为它是一个严格控温的环境
as it's a temperature-controlled environment.
接下来去我们世界顶级的育马场
So let's move on to our world class stud farm...
见见三位肯塔基赛马冠军
and meet three of our Kentucky Derby winners.
生物扫描安保就为了保护
Biometric security scanner just to protect
几桶旧威士忌
a few old barrels of whiskey?
骗谁呢宝贝
Pull the other one, love.
好了
Got it.
你发现什么了吗
Are you getting anything?
还没有
Not yet.
我了个去
Fucking hell.
可惜不是苏格兰威士忌
It's a shame it's not scotch.
等一下
Hang on.
从这上面看  我们正下方
According to this, there's a huge
有个巨大的地下设施
underground structure right beneath us.
如果我的计算是正确的
And if my calculations are correct...
这个
This...
就是入口
is the way in.
他妈的  梅林  我去
Fucking hell, Merlin. Shit.
你知道么  我妈妈
You know, my mama...
他总是跟我说
she always told me...
我们南方人的礼貌都是从英国人那里来的
us southerners get our good manners from the British.
我就在想  这可太遗憾了
I was thinkin', ain't that a pity.
你们自己怎么没留下来多少
Y'all didn't keep nothing for yourselves.
联邦英雄
肯塔基纯波本威士忌
你们都没听说过进之前先敲门么
Y'all ain't never heard of knocking before you enter?
其实我们是收到邀请的  不是吗
Well, actually we had an invitation. Didn't we?
哦又有邀请了
Yeah. Oh, did you now?
是的  邀请函是个瓶子的形式
Yeah. It came in the shape of a bottle.
我们来自伦敦的皇家绅士裁缝铺
We're from the Kingsman tailor shop in London.
也许你听说过我们
Maybe you've heard of us?
哦  皇家绅士
Oh, the Kingsman.
- 嗯  - 嗯
- Yeah. - Huh.
你们的漂亮衣服和时髦的眼镜
That's where y'all got them fine suits
就是打那儿来的
and them fancy spectacles y'all got on?
- 正是  - 就是这样
- Exactly. - That's right.
你们看上去真漂亮
Y'all look damn sharp.
我看看我又没有搞对
Let me see if I got it right, here.
你们想让我相信  一个裁缝  只用一个小破手表
You want me to believe that it's normal for a tailor...
就能黑进一个高端生物安保系统
to hack through an advanced biometric security system...
没什么稀奇的
with nothing but a little bitty old watch on?
我向你保证
I can promise you...
门都没有
that dog don't hunt.
所以你们不如给我跪在地上
So why don't you go on and get down on your knees...
告诉我你们到底替谁卖命的
and tell me who you really work for.
那是1963联邦英雄珍藏
That's 1963 Statesman Reserve.
你把这事变成私人恩怨了
You just made it personal.
击昏
你他妈是谁啊
Who the fuck are you?
一堵秘密墙壁里的瓶子
A bottle in a secret wall.
你们指望我把这种话当真
You really expect me to take that seriously?
你看  我觉得你们的故事是马粪
See, I think your story's horse shit.
你们只是想掩盖一个失败的救援任务
Y'all just trying to cover for a failed rescue mission.
你们是为那个昆虫学家而来  是吧
You here for the lepidopterist, ain't you?
好  所以你们的神秘瓶子
Okay, so your mystery bottle, huh?
像不像这个
Look anything like that, right there?
对  同一个牌子  老得多
Yes. Same brand, much older.
好
All right.
咱们说说
Let's see here.
你们知道为什么
You know why the measurement
酒精含量的量度叫  证明么
of alcohol content's called "proof"?
哦去你妈的吧
Oh, fuck off!
哦他妈的
Oh, for Pete's sake.
这个词来自过去的时候
See, comes from back in the old days...
海盗们想要检验他们的朗姆酒的浓度
when pirates wanted to test the strength of their rum.
他们就会倒一点点在火药上
They used to pour a little bit out on gunpowder.
我去  这能让你打你妈妈一巴掌
That'll make you wanna slap your mama right there, boy.
如果火药
And if the gunpowder,
如果火药能点着
if it burnt when they set it alight...
他们就会认为这证明了
they considered it proof...
他们的朗姆酒又好又烈
that their rum was good and strong.
不过  我身上又没有火药  对吧
But see, I ain't got no gunpowder on me, do I?
但是我能保证我把你们的蛋蛋点着的时候
But I'm pretty sure you boys'll make
你们两个小伙子
just as impressive of a sound...
喊出的声音一样响
when I set your balls on fire.
或者你们也可以直接告诉我你们他妈到底是谁
Or you could just tell me who the fuck y'all really are...
你们怎么找到我们的
and how the hell y'all found us.
听着  我最后再说一遍
Look, for the last time,
我们除了荣誉之外没有什么好保护的
we have nothing to protect but our honor.
所以你可以拿走你叫做威士忌的
So you can take your cheap horse piss
廉价马尿
that you call whiskey...
对了  它的拼写没有那个e
which, by the way, is spelled without an "e"...
也完全比不上单一麦芽苏格兰威士忌
and is nothing compared to a single malt scotch...
然后去干你自己吧
and you can go fuck yourself.
那你呢
What about you?
- 我  - 嗯
- Me? - Yeah.
我爱死杰克丹尼兑可乐了  老哥
No, I love a Jack and Coke, bruv.
但是你干你自己那部分我完全同意
But I do agree with the part where you go fuck yourself.
好吧
All right.
你们除了荣誉之外
Y'all ain't got nothing to protect
没什么好保护的
other than your honor.
来看看我们把事情变变会发生什么
Let's see what happens when we change things up.
- 我操  - 哈利
- Fuck me. - Harry?
你们有三秒钟时间告诉我真相
Y'all got three seconds to tell me the truth.
等等  不要
Wait. No.
- 不要  - 哈利
No! Harry!
他听不见你  但我能  所以快说
He can't hear you. But I can, so talk.
- 不要  - 躲开  哈利
- No! - Get down, Harry!
- 哈利  哈利  - 两秒了
Harry! Harry! That's two.
- 哈利  - 哈利
- Harry! - Harry!
- 哈利  - 三
- Harry! - Three.
停
Stop!
他们的故事没问题
Their story checked out.
我打开礼物我们的末日方案柜
I opened our doomsday scenario locker
然后那个雨伞在里面
and that umbrella was in it.
皇家绅士  上面有我们的标记
Kingsman. It's got our logo on it.
我真抱歉
I'm really sorry.
对不起了  小伙子们
My apologies, boys.
我希望你们别太难过
I hope there ain't no hard feelings.
我只是在做我的工作
I was just doin' my job.
欢迎来到联邦特工
Welcome to the Statesman,
独立情报机构
independent intelligence agency.
就像你们一样  我猜
Just like y'all, I reckon.
不过我们的创始人从事了酒类行业
But our founders went into the booze business.
感谢上天
Thank the sweet Lord above.
这位是姜汁汽水
This is Ginger Ale.
她是我们的战略主任
She's our strategy executive.
你们好
Hello.
我是龙舌兰特工
I'm Agent Tequila.
现在是你该给我们松绑的时候了
This is the part where you untie us.
谢谢
Thank you.
哈利
Harry.
- 你好  - 你好  朋友
- Hello. - Hello, mate.
哈利
Harry.
你好
How do you do?
我们见过吗
Have we met before?
哈利  没事的  没事  他们知道我们认识你
Harry, it's okay. It's fine. They know that we know you.
我觉得你们肯定搞错了
I think there must be some mistake.
过去好久了  哈利
It's been such a long time, Harry.
我该换我的粗格鞋底了
I need to get my brogues resoled.
我的牛津鞋也是这样的
Yeah, and my oxfords are done in as well.
你为什么在和我讲你的鞋子
Why are you telling me about your shoes?
我是个鳞翅目昆虫学家
I'm a lepidopterist.
你是个啥
You're a what?
我研究蝴蝶
I study butterflies.
夜蛾科
你入伍之前是想过  但是
Well, you wanted to be before you joined the army, but...
哈利  看着我
Harry, look at me.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
我们马上回来
We'll be back soon.
这些家伙就是我们的末日协议
So these fellas right here are our doomsday protocol?
才发现  我们创始人的裁缝是皇家绅士
Turns out, our founder's tailor was Kingsman.
你们他妈对他做了什么
What the fuck have you done to him?
什么都没有  只有试图帮助他
Nothing. Only tried to help him.
他患了退行性失忆症
He's got retrograde amnesia.
我们从他的眼镜看出来
Now, we knew from his eyeglasses
他是情报机构的人
that he was intelligence.
我们就是不知道是哪家
We just didn't know whose.
他怎么跑到这里来的
How did he get here?
一年前
肯塔基州
什么鬼
What the hell?
龙舌兰  我这里收到了一个超高的
Tequila, I'm getting a crazy spike...
低频波的尖峰  距这里18公里
of extreme low frequency waves 11 miles from here.
我需要你马上送我过去
I'm gonna need you to escort me there immediately.
我需要你的阿尔法凝胶
I need your alpha gel.
我去检查教堂
I'll go check the church.
我们发明了阿尔法凝胶技术
We developed our alpha gel technology
给我们自己的特工
for our own agents...
用在头部中弹的情况下
in the event of a head shot.
凝胶保护大脑
The gel protects the brain.
然后在实验室里我们用纳奈
Then, in the lab, we use nanites...
微型机器人  来修复组织损伤
micro-bots, to repair tissue damage.
但是有副作用
There are side effects.
部分  失忆症
Partial amnesia...
退回年轻的自己
regression to the younger self.
完全不知道自己是谁  我们也没办法
With no idea who he was, there was nothing we could do.
但是现在你们在这里了
But now you guys are here...
我们有很大几率把他带回来
there's a good chance we can bring him back.
罂粟国度
你来晚了
You're late.
你怎么还穿着那个
Why are you still wearing that?
在你撤掉周边的地雷之前
Until you get rid of the perimeter landmines...
我都会穿着这套衣服的  非常感谢
I'll keep wearing the suit, thank you very much.
胆小鬼
Scaredy-cat.
闭嘴  坐下
Shut up and sit down.
开始
Let's go!
鳄鱼摇滚  谢谢
Crocodile Rock, please.
你麻痹
Fuck you!
嘿嘿  艾尔顿  主意用词
Hey, hey, Elton, language.
好  你既然会的那么多
Okay, as fabulous as your catalogue is...
我想听段格什温
I think I want to hear some Gershwin.
我实在不敢相信
I still can't believe...
你成功绑架了艾尔顿·约翰
you got away with kidnapping Elton John.
我知道  但是瓦伦丁绑架了那么多名人
I know! But with Valentine abducting those celebrities...
不趁乱占点便宜就太蠢了
it seemed silly not to take advantage of the confusion.
我去  艾尔顿得了那个蓝疹子
Shit. Has Elton got the blue rash?
灯
Lights.
嘿  艾尔顿
Hey, Elton.
你是不是又干坏事了
Have you been a bad boy again?
没有
Mmm-mmm.
你骗人  看你的手
You're lying. Look at your hands.
这是什么
What is it?
这是我的计划会见效的证明
It's proof that my plan is gonna work.
这也是一个漫长而恐怖的死亡的第一个标志
It's also the first sign of a slow and horrible death.
别担心  我会治好的
Don't worry, I can fix it.
告诉我你和谁狂欢了
Tell me who you partied with.
是天使
It was Angel.
不是很有天使风范啊
Huh, not very angelic.
我得把他的翅膀剪了
Gonna have to clip his wings.
把门关上
Close the door behind you.
你什么时候才能像一个
At what point are you going to start behaving
联邦英雄一样呢  龙舌兰
like a Statesman, Tequila?
你还想回去当一个骑牛的小丑么
You wanna go back to being a rodeo clown?
不想  长官  我道歉  长官
No, sir. I apologize, sir.
我是香槟
I'm Champagne.
但是识相的人
But anyone who knows what's good for him...
都叫我头儿
calls me Champ.
冠军的简称
你们受苦了我很抱歉
Sorry for your troubles.
作为你们在美国的表亲
As your American cousins...
我把联邦英雄大得多的资源任你支配
I'm placing all of Statesman's considerably larger resources at your disposal.
联邦英雄酿酒厂市值
你能想象服装业能有这个数么
Can you imagine those in the clothing business?
好了  有什么可以帮你的
Now, how can I help you?
首先  我得感谢你们
First of all, I've got to thank you
救了加拉哈德特工
for saving Agent Galahad.
等等
Wait.
你说你是加拉哈德
You said that you were Galahad.
不是  他是在说那个蝴蝶男
Oh, no, he's talking about the butterfly guy.
- 这曾经是他的代号  - 哦
- That used to be his handle. - Oh.
加拉哈德总是说
Galahad always said,
你需要看到全景
"You've got to look at the bigger picture..."
问  是谁  的同时也要问  为何
"ask 'why' as well as 'who'."
所以如果有人想要干掉王牌特工
So if someone wanted to take out Kingsman...
那他们肯定在策划什么大事
then they've got to be planning something major.
所以你知道什么
So what do you know?
他们是一个贩毒集团  我们认为
They're a drug cartel, we think.
黄金圈这个名字总是冒出来
The name Golden Circle keeps coming up.
嗯  我们会调查他们  还有什么
Mmm. We'll look into them. What else?
我们一个前学员在为他们卖命
One of our former trainees is working with them.
查理·赫斯基斯  混球一个
Charlie Hesketh. Total prick.
你有关于他的好的线索吗
You got any promising leads on him?
他的前女友
His ex-girlfriend.
我在社交网络上跟踪关注了她一段时间
I've been tracking her through social media.
我们相信他们之间确实还有联系
We believe she's still in contact with him.
她还准备去参加格拉斯顿伯里音乐节
And she's going to Glastonbury Music Festival.
哦  很好
Oh, good.
龙舌兰特工  把你的舞鞋找出来吧
Agent Tequila, break out your dancing shoes.
你又有活儿干了
You have a new mission.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
稍等
Hold up.
你身体怎么样
You feeling okay?
我就是有点累  但是还好  谢谢关心
I'm a little tired, but fine, thanks.
加拉哈德  准备好了吗
Galahad, you ready?
你脸上
Your face...
有点儿
You got...
这是什么情况
What the fuck?
哦  见鬼
Oh, shit.
快去医务室吧
Head to the sick bay.
让金杰给你检查检查
Have Ginger check you out.
等等  把你眼镜给他
Hey, give him your glasses.
你走运了  小子  戴上眼睛
You're in luck, kid. Put 'em on.
会有我们这里最优秀的资深特工
You get our finest senior agent
来加入你的任务
to join you instead.
现在这会儿  他在我们纽约的分部呢
Right now, he's in our New York office.
加拉哈德  这位是威士忌特工
Galahad, meet Agent Whiskey.
孩子
Kid...
看起来我们得去摇滚音乐会上泡妞了
looks like we're hookin' up with a chick at a rock concert.
这是我最喜欢的任务
My favorite kind of mission.
我会派我的飞机去接你的
I'm sending my jet to pick you up.
联邦特工
我们以前曾经治疗过这种失忆症
We've dealt with this kind of amnesia before.
哈利就像是一台需要重启的计算机
Harry's like a computer that needs to be rebooted.
我们需要重现他过去所受过的惊吓或者是创伤
We need to recreate a shock or trauma from his past...
好来唤醒他的记忆
to trigger his memory.
逃脱训练
希望你是对的
I hope you're right.
额  有人吗
Uh, excuse me.
这里看起来好像是出了什么问题
There seems to be some sort of a problem here.
救命呀  有人吗
Help! Somebody!
这他妈的是什么情况  救命呀
What the hell is going on? Help me!
救命呀
Help!
天呐
Oh, God!
停下  妈的
Stop! Fuck!
把他弄出来吧
Get him out now.
不  不  等等  他的本能马上就能觉醒了
No, no, wait. His instincts are gonna kick in.
不  我很抱歉这样做
No. I'm sorry to do this.
取消
- 你没事吧  - 刚刚是什么情况
- Are you okay? - What happened?
哈利  你不记得自己是谁了
Harry, you've forgotten who you are.
我们觉得这么做可能会唤起你的记忆
We thought this might jog your memory.
听着  你还年轻的时候  曾经有过一次选择
Look, when you were young, you had a choice.
要么去当鳞翅昆虫学家要么就是去参军
To either be a lepidopterist or to join the army.
你选择了后者  直到加入了皇家特工组织
You chose the army. That led to Kingsman.
你成为了一名皇家特工
You became a Kingsman agent.
我觉得我不会给任何会用水来
I doubt whether I'd work for anyone
溺死下属的人工作的
who drowns their employees.
我想回家
I want to go home.
我要带走我的蝴蝶标本
I want my butterfly collection.
我想见我母亲了
I want to see Mother.
我们已经没什么能做的了
There's nothing more we can do.
是时候让他离开了
It's time to let him go.
宝贝儿  我也想待的时间长一些
Babe, I wish I could stay longer,
但是我得去执行这次的任务了
but I've got to go on with this mission.
等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
在你走之前  我想给你看个东西
Before you go, I wanna show you something.
我知道JB是不可取代的
I know he could never replace JB...
但是
but...
我的天啊
Oh, my days.
希望他能够让你开心点儿
I hoped he might make you happy.
顺便给你找一个早点回家的理由
And give you another reason to come back home soon.
我很喜欢
I love him.
但是我已经不再需要别的回家理由了
But I don't need another reason to come home.
我很抱歉  只是在等我的朋友
I apologize. Just waiting for my friend.
我会尽早回来的  我向你保证
I'll be back as soon as I can, I promise.
- 又要去拯救世界了  - 对的
- Got to go save the world? - Yep.
好吧  如果你能拯救世界
Well, if you save the world...
你知道有什么奖励
you know what that means.
是啊  没问题
Yeah, all right.
再见了  小家伙
Bye, buddy.
我可是托关系才拿到了通行证
Got the passes from my contact.
你会爱死格拉斯顿伯里的
You're gonna love Glastonbury.
好吧  这有什么难的  孩子
Well, that's the easy part, kid.
你看看手套箱里是什么
Take a look in the glove box.
我的天啊  兄弟
Fucking hell, bruv.
我还以为美国的什么东西都应该更大呢
Thought everything was supposed to be bigger in America.
这就是你会开这种特大跑车来补偿的原因吗
Is this why you overcompensate with these massive cars?
套在你的手指上面
Goes on your finger.
指尖上装有追踪追踪器
The surveillance tracker is in the tip.
轻轻按住三秒就会释放出来
Apply light pressure for three seconds to release it.
格拉斯顿伯里音乐节
好了  根据她在INS上的更新
Okay, so according to her Instagram feed...
查理的前女友现在在贵宾酒吧里面
Charlie's ex-girlfriend is up ahead at the VIP bar.
咱们两个谁去放出追踪器
Which one of us is gonna plant the tracker?
看看腕带  伙计们
Bands, boys.
好的  可以进去了
Yeah, that's fine.
我觉得我们都应该试试
I say we both make an approach...
谁水准更高  谁就上
whoever gets on best, goes for it.
好吧  我觉得不用搞这种比赛吧  兄弟
Well, it doesn't have to be a competition, bruv.
为什么我们不直接走过去
Why don't we just go up to her...
握握她的手  摸摸她的后背
shake her hand, pat her on the back,
无论怎样  你知道  很简单的
whatever, you know. Job done.
手上可没有什么黏膜  艾格西
The hand is not a mucous membrane, Eggsy.
背上也没有
Neither is the back.
皇家特工都教你什么了呀
They teach you anything at Kingsman?
你在说什么呀
What are you talking about?
我们的追踪器可以跟着体内的血液循环
Our trackers are designed to enter the bloodstream.
对人体无害  并且能传输音频和定位信号
They circulate harmlessly, providing full audio and GPS.
黏膜
Mucus membrane.
鼻子里面那种黏膜  对吧
That's like up the nose, isn't it?
你他妈的让我怎么办  把我手指插进
What the fuck am I gonna do? Stick my finger...
不是插进鼻子里面  对吧
It's not just inside the nose, is it?
- 对  艾格西  不是  - 妈蛋
- No, Eggsy, it ain't. - Fuck.
好了  我先来吧
All right, I'll take the first crack.
你可看好了  兄弟
Watch and learn, buddy.
祝你好运
Good luck.
- 请用  女士  - 谢谢你
- Here you go, ma'am. - Thank you.
小姐  不好意思
Miss, I beg your pardon.
听着  我不是有意打扰你的
Now, I don't wanna pester you...
但是我只是想知道  你几点上台表演
but I just have to know, what time are you playing?
我不是乐队里的
I'm not in a band.
天啊  你以为我是谁
Oh, God. Who did you think I was?
可别是哪个不招人待见的家伙
Please don't say someone ghastly.
我的妈呀  感觉自己就像个锤子
God damn it, now I feel like a fool.
我只是觉得像你这么魅力十足的女士
I just assumed that a woman with your charisma...
好吧  肯定不是平常人
well, she just had to be somebody.
是吗
Right.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
不  没事的  我知道你不是有意
No, it's okay. I know you didn't mean
让我看起来像个傻子一样
to make me feel like a dumb-ass.
所以我会让你补偿我一下
So I'll let you make it up to me
让我请你喝几杯酒
by letting me buy you a drink.
看着我的手指
Follow my finger.
你在做什么
What are we doing?
往左翻下一张相片
Swiping to the left.
什么  在美国你都不用探探的嘛
What, you don't do Tinder in America?
探什么呀
Tinder what?
你知道吗  我想这可能就是代沟吧
Do you know, I think it's probably a generational thing.
翻译过来就是  离我远点  老杂毛
It translates as "Go away, old man."
保重  再见
Be good, be cool.
再见
Bye.
谢谢你为我解围
Thank you for that.
- 我叫克拉拉  - 我是里弗
- I'm Clara. - River.
我的天呐  都这个点儿了
Bloody hell, is that the time?
你知道吗  我时差还没倒过来
You know what, I'm so jetlagged
我甚至不知道自己去了哪里
I don't know if I'm coming or going.
你都去哪儿了  有好玩的地方吗
Where've you been? Anywhere nice?
南美洲  我在那里可待了一阵子
South America. Been spending a bit of time out there.
跟着一个萨满训练
Training with the shaman,
试着能跟我的精神动物建立起来联系
and trying to really connect with my spirit animal.
- 是吗  - 我的是只乌鸦
- Yeah. - I'm a crow.
还有  等等  我来猜猜
And, hang on, let me guess...
- 算了  - 美洲豹
- No. - Jaguar.
什么  不会吧  我的天
What? No! Oh, my God!
- 猜对了  - 你是怎么知道的
- Yes? - How did you even know that?
你看  真的是美洲豹  你看看
Look, it totally is. Check it out.
哦  部落图腾 黑色美洲豹 很厉害
Oh. . Black jaguar. Very nice.
不如这样吧  我来请你喝一杯
You know what? I wanna buy you a drink.
艾格西从格拉斯顿伯里发过来的
Eggsy sent this from Glastonbury.
蓝色皮疹 /   调查结果
蓝色皮疹  在推特上掀起了热潮
And #bluerash is trending on Twitter.
那你找到这些病例之间的相互关系了吗
Have you found any correlation between these cases?
只有吸食消遣性毒品
Only recreational drug use.
我懂  这不像联邦特工该干的事
I know. Not very Statesman-like.
龙舌兰
Tequila here...
一直是我们这儿的坏小子
he is our resident bad boy.
你不觉得这件事情可能会
You don't think this could be related
跟黄金圈有吗  不是吗
to The Golden Circle, do you?
毒品垄断集团毒害自己的顾客吗
A drug cartel poisoning its customers?
这说不通啊
Doesn't make sense.
罂粟国度
罂粟  你能把糖递给我好吗
Poppy, would you pass the sugar, please?
好的
Okay.
但糖对你的身体可不好啊
But it's really bad for you.
糖的成瘾性是可卡因的八倍之多
Eight times more addictive than cocaine.
致死的可能性也有五倍之多
Five times more likely to cause death.
但是是合法的
But it's legal...
所以  你请便  想加多少加多少
so, you go ahead. Knock yourself out.
不要在我面前提起烟草和酒精
Don't get me started on tobacco and alcohol.
兜售烟酒的都进了世界五百强了
Peddle that stuff and you're in Fortune 500.
我呢  没门
But me? No!
我只能躲在
I'm out here hiding
这个穷乡僻壤的地方  思乡成疾
in the middle of nowhere. Homesick.
因为我卖的是毒品
Because I sell drugs.
哦  波波  你这么做是因为很想念家乡吗
Oh, Pops. You're doing this because you're homesick?
是的
Yes.
我想要的是自由
I want freedom.
我还想扬名天下
I want fame.
我们去年的利润达到了两千五百亿美元
Our profits were 250 billion dollars last year.
我是最最成功的女商人
I am the most successful businesswoman
在世界上  但是没人认识我
in the world, but nobody knows who I am.
波波  波波
Pops, Pops.
不用花多久时间了
It's not long now, eh?
你说得对  谢谢你
You're right, thank you.
抱歉打扰到你们
Sorry to interrupt you.
你想要见我吗  罂粟女士
You wanted to see me, Madam Poppy?
是的  安格尔  在黄金圈
Yes, Angel. In The Golden Circle...
我们不准试用商品
we do not sample the merchandise...
我们也不能破坏规矩
and we do not break the rules.
这就是我为什么会在机器人身上投资
Which is why I have invested in robots...
因为它们比人类更可靠
because they are so much more reliable
更值得信任
and trustworthy than human beings.
埃尔顿·约翰
友方
真可惜我们没能找到你的朋友们
Sorry we never found your friends.
好吧  我们大家分道而行
Well, we all go on our separate journeys...
但是  最终  我们会到达
but, ultimately, we'll all arrive
同一个终点
at the same destination.
我们还看看我的帐篷吗  以防他们会在里面
Shall we check my tent? See if they're there?
- 好  - 哦  过来吧
- Yeah. - Oh, come on.
哇哦
Wow.
这里太棒了
This is amazing.
坐吧
Come on.
额  你知道吗  我觉得自己要先去尿个尿
Uh, you know what, I'm busting for a pee actually.
你想的话  可以弄到我身体里
You could do it on me if you want.
稍等一下
Maybe in a bit.
给我一分钟  好吗
Give me a sec, yeah?
好的  但是要快点  里弗
Okay, but hurry up, River.
等了一晚上就是为了最后和你亲亲呀
Been waiting all night for you to at least kiss me.
嘿
Hey!
你好呀  宝贝  遇到点麻烦
Hi, babe. Uh, bit of a nightmare.
我需要跟一个目标任务上床
I've got to sleep with a target...
但是要是你不同意的话  我就不做了
but I won't do it, unless you agree that it's all right.
你特么的是在耍我吗
You've got to be fucking kidding.
我算什么  练习对象吗
What was I, target practice?
宝贝  我现在就跟你说实话
Babe, surely it's better that I'm honest with you...
好过我做了之后还不告诉你吧
rather than me doing it and not telling you.
这可是拯救世界的紧急任务呢
Kind of got a bit of a "save the world" situation here.
跟别人特么的乱搞
How the fuck is screwing someone
就能拯救世界了
gonna save the world?
好吧  可能是有点儿复杂
Well, it's a bit complicated...
但是相信我  不到万不得已我是不会这么做的
but trust me, I would not be doing it if I didn't have to.
宝贝儿  请你相信我  我爱你
Babe, please believe me. I love you.
你是那个我想要一起度过
You are the person I wanna spend
我的下半生的人
the rest of my life with.
这算是求婚吗
Is that a proposal?
因为我觉得我会允许你这么做
Because I think I'd give you my permission.
在有安全保证的  和知道了我们这个承诺的前提下
Having that security, knowing that we were committed...
在这种情况下  是的  我会觉得不一样
In that context, yeah. Yeah, I'd feel different.
好吧  我说的是
Right. Well, I mean...
我想和你在一起
I want to be with you,
但是成为公众人物的话  宝贝
but being a public figure, babe...
比方说亲王的话
like a prince...
会有这种困扰  你知道吗
It's a bit of a factor, you know,
这会影响到我的工作
what with my job and stuff.
哦  不  不  不  别呀  好了
Oh, no, no, no, come on. Okay.
听着  我们得正式地谈一谈这件事情
Uh, look, we need to talk about this properly.
只要等我五分钟  好吗
Just give me five minutes, okay?
别这么瞧不起自己  艾格西
Don't put yourself down, Eggsy.
我确定你能坚持的更久一些
I'm sure you can last longer than that.
- 怎么了  - 没什么
- What's the matter? - Nothing.
我只是觉得我们的精神动物
I just feel that our spirit animals
还需要一些时间来磨合
need more time to get in sync...
来找到精神境界上的默契联系
and find a harmonious bond on the spiritual plane.
说得好
Totally.
是吧
Yeah?
或者我们应该直接
Or we could just...
开始
fuck?
克拉拉  我觉得我做不到
Clara, I don't think I can.
但是你猜怎么着
But you know what?
我的乌鸦现在需要个巢穴休息一下
My crow is looking for a place to nest.
格拉斯顿伯里
干得漂亮  艾格西
Good work, Eggsy!
追踪器运转正常
Tracker fully functional.
不用担心  之前和威士忌搭档的时候也有过这种情况
Don't worry, I've been through this with Whiskey before.
跟一个知道自己在干什么的特工
Nice to be working with an agent
一起工作还是不错的
who knows what he's doing.
哇哦  乌鸦先生  该我了
Wow, Mr. Crow. My turn.
抱歉  我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't.
我正在谈恋爱呢
I'm in a relationship.
什么大不了呀  知道吗  我也有男朋友
That's adorable. Listen, so am I.
今日事今日毕  不必带到明天去
What happens at Glasto, stays in Glasto.
我做不到
I can't.
再见  克拉拉
Bye, Clara.
我是蒂尔德公主
This is Princess T,
请留言
please leave a message.
这里是墨托庄园酒店
Motor Manor Hotel...
麻烦帮我叫蒂尔德公主接一下电话好吗
Yeah, can you put me through to Princess Tilde, please.
哦  事实上  先生  我刚刚看了看电脑记录
Oh, actually, sir, I'm just looking at my computer...
而我恐怕公主
and I'm afraid that the princess
已经退房了
is already checked out.
谢谢你
Thank you.
妈的
Fuck!
哈利
Harry.
- 你在干什么  - 我只是在收拾行李
- What's going on? - I was just packing.
看看这些可爱的洗漱用品
Look at these lovely toiletries
梅林送给了我这些用品当作是离别礼物
Merlin very kindly gave me as a leaving present.
你看  试试这个须后水
Here, try this aftershave.
好吧  我知道  哈利  我用的就是这个
Yeah, I know, Harry. I'm wearing it.
听着  你不能这么放弃
Listen, you can't just give up.
放弃吗
Give up?
不是  正好相反  我就要实现梦想了
No, on the contrary. I'm about to achieve my dream.
研究那些稀有蝴蝶
Researching rare butterflies
和那些最优秀的昆虫学家一起工作
alongside some of the finest minds in entomology.
蛱蝶科
闪蛱蝶亚科
你知道吗  你也许该把我钉到这墙上
You know, you may as well have me stuck up on this wall.
因为你可是找不到比我更有趣的蝴蝶了
'Cause you're never gonna find a butterfly more interesting than me.
什么
Sorry?
我们刚见面的时候  我只是  像是  一条蛆虫
When you and I first met, I was just, like, a maggot.
蛆虫长大会变成苍蝇
Maggots turn into flies.
你想说的是幼虫吧
Perhaps you mean larva.
幼虫  对  是的  无所谓了  重点是
Larva, yeah, okay. Whatever. The point is...
大家都看不起我
everyone wanted to squash me.
但你不是
But not you.
你帮助我变成了毛毛虫
You helped me to become a caterpillar.
而现在我破茧成蝶了
And now I've got wings.
我从没有想过自己还能飞到这么高
I'm flying higher than I ever dreamed.
而这一切都多亏了你
And that is all thanks to you.
我讨厌不礼貌  但是我觉得我得赶紧收拾
I hate to seem rude, but I need to finish packing
然后休息休息
and get some sleep.
哈利  你不能就这么一走了之
Harry, you can't just walk away.
皇家特工需要你
Kingsman needs you.
全世界都需要你
The whole world needs you.
我需要你
I need you.
艾格西  恐怕  你说的那个
Eggy, whoever the Harry was
哈利无论是谁  他都已经不在了
that you knew, he's gone, I'm afraid.
再见了
Goodbye.
这可不是马提尼
That's not a martini.
在肯塔基州就是
It is in Kentucky.
没毛病
Fair enough.
敬你一杯  艾格西
Here's to you, Eggsy.
你正是王牌特工需要的人
You're exactly what Kingsman needs.
我是蒂尔达女王储
This is Princess T.
请留言
Please leave a message.
可以再给我一杯马提尼吗
Can I have another martini, please?
好的
Sure.
谢了
Thanks.
你还好吗
我真的要和你谈谈
蒂尔达拜托了
宝贝
拜托  我真的有事跟你说
来自艾格西
宝贝我从来没像现在这样需要你
我爱你  希望你安好
放弃吧
Give up.
宠物商店
市中心宠物店
你造吗
You know what?
这是我喝过最好喝的马提尼了
That was the best martini I've ever had.
不用找了
Keep the change.
谢谢
Thanks.
没关系  别害怕
It's all right. Don't panic.
我只是想给你带一个临别礼物
Just thought I'd bring you a little leaving present.
你喜欢吗  很可爱吧
What do you think? He's lovely, isn't he?
你想抱抱吗
Would you like to hold him?
你好呀
Hello.
我应该开枪打他吗
Do you think I should shoot him?
- 你疯了  - 怎么了  有什么问题
Are you quite mad? What? What's the problem?
- 不行  不能这样  - 怎么呢
No! You can't! Eh? What?
- 不  你先杀了我  - 杀你
No, you'll have to shoot me! Shoot you?
我可以杀你
Well, I will shoot you.
不  没有人这么变态忍心杀小狗
No. No one's sick enough to shoot a puppy!
那你呢  哈利
Well, what about you, Harry?
你就忍心杀小狗
You were sick enough to shoot a puppy!
你记得吗
Do you remember?
你就忍心杀小狗
You were sick enough to shoot a puppy!
腌黄瓜先生
- 那是空弹  - 没错  哈利
It was a blank. Yes, Harry. Yes!
那是空弹
It was a fucking blank!
没错  那是空弹
That's right. It was a blank!
我绝不可能伤害腌黄瓜先生
I would never hurt Mr. Pickle!
没错  哈利  它活到了很老
Yes, Harry! He lived to a ripe old age!
最后是得了胰腺炎死的
He died of pancreatitis!
你不是腌黄瓜先生
You're not Mr. Pickle.
艾格西
Eggsy.
你好  哈利
Hello, Harry.
艾格西
Eggsy.
- 必须有人阻止瓦伦丁  - 我知道
Valentine has to be stopped. No, I know.
- 他有一个装置  - 没关系
He has a device. It's all right.
被处理好了  别担心
It's sorted. Don't worry.
有很多事要和你讲解
We got a lot of catching up to do.
好吧好吧
Well, well.
看来我应该取消预约的出租车了
I suppose I should cancel that taxi.
是的
Yes.
如果你不介意的话
If you don't mind...
梅林
Merlin.
欢迎回来
Welcome back...
加拉哈德
Galahad.
我们汇报完了情况  哈利
Now that we've finished the debrief, Harry...
我们有欢迎礼物要给你
here's a couple of welcome back gifts.
首先
First up...
全新的王牌特工手表
a brand-new Kingsman watch.
内含高科技软件
Advanced software,
能黑进任何含有微芯片的东西
it can hack into anything with a microchip.
酷毙了
It is the bollocks.
梅林
And Merlin...
我给你做了这个
I made you these.
谢谢你  梅林  艾格西
Thank you, Merlin, Eggsy.
- 我戴着咋么样  - 你戴着
How do I look? You look...
像一个眼睛欠操的基佬
Like some faggot lookin' for an eye fuckin'.
听着
Now...
不如你们滚出我的酒吧
why don't you get out of our bar...
不然我就把你另一只眼睛挖出去
before I take out your other one?
听着  你这是欢迎外地人的
Now, is that any way to welcome a visitor
方式吗  白月光
from out of town, moonshine?
好吧
Okay.
我的南方大屌给你吸
Suck my southern dick...
贱人
bitch.
这应该不用了吧
Oh, I don't think that'll be necessary.
拜拜  先生
Good day, sir.
所以呢
Well?
你们几个娘们磨蹭什么呢
What are you ladies waitin' for?
明礼
Manners...
方能
maketh...
成人
man.
你知道是什么意思吗
Do you know what that means?
不知道我就来教教你
Then let me teach you a lesson.
打算在这里大眼瞪小眼一整天吗
Are we going to stand around here all day?
还是说我们要
Or are we going to...
你个大
You big...
把他拉起来
Well, pick him up.
这可不算是正宗的肯塔基式欢迎
Now, that is not what I call a Kentucky welcome.
明礼方能成人
Manners maketh man.
我来给你们解释一下
Let me translate that for you.
我怎么了  梅林
What's wrong with me, Merlin?
我以为你治好我了
I thought you fixed me?
我们重塑了你的神经通路
Well, we rebuilt your neural pathways.
但协调还需要一些时间
But it'll take time to get your coordination back.
那些蝴蝶幻象呢
And the phantom butterflies?
你会犯病
You will experience episodes...
失去清醒的神志
lapses of clarity.
很快你就正常了
You'll be back to normal soon.
感觉自己像是横扫拖车公园的龙卷风
I feel like a tornado in a trailer park.
♪黄金圈荣誉出品♪
♪ Golden Circle proudly presents ♪
总统先生  我叫罂粟·亚当斯
Mr. President, my name is Poppy Adams.
我认为联合国没有种
I believe the UN has no teeth.
所以选择了您  作为自由世界的领导人
So I've selected you, as leader of the free world,
来一起沟通
to receive this communication.
我邀请您开始商议
And I invite you to begin negotiations...
历史上规模最大的绑架事件
on the largest scale hostage situation in history.
波比制药厂
几周前
A few weeks ago,
一种人工研制的病毒被传播了出去
an engineered virus was released...
该病毒潜伏在我们公司的各种产品中
contained in all varieties of my product.
例如大麻  可卡因  海洛因  鸦片  兴奋剂
Cannabis, cocaine, heroin, opium, ecstasy...
还有冰毒等
...and crystal meth.
你们中的有些人已经感染了
Some of you are already infected.
接下来几天你将会
And this is what you can expect
经历这些事
in the coming days.
在短暂的潜伏期后
After a brief incubation period...
受害者会出现第一阶段症状
victims present with stage one symptoms.
蓝色皮疹
A blue rash.
接下来
Next...
第二阶段症状出现了
second stage symptoms appear.
躁狂
Mania...
同时病毒进入大脑
as the virus enters the brain.
对受害者和身边的人来说
Very distressing to the victim
都很痛苦
and those around them.
第三阶段
Stage three...
瘫痪
Paralysis.
肌肉进入灾难性癫痫状态
Muscles enter a state of catastrophic seizure.
当胸肌受到影响后
And once the muscles of the thorax become affected...
就无法呼吸了
breathing becomes impossible...
在12小时内导致一场非常难看的死亡
leading to a very nasty death within 12 hours.
但对于数百万的感染患者  我有好消息
But I have good news to the millions already affected.
你们没必要这样死去
It doesn't have to be this way.
我有解药
I have an antidote.
你对我做了什么  你个臭婊子
What have you done to me, you fucking bitch?
百分百有效
100% effective...
已经准备好运往世界各地
and ready to ship out worldwide
下单立即发货
at a moment's notice.
- 滚出我房间  - 我向你们保证
Get out of my room! You have my word.
- 出去  - 上述承诺我可以实现
Get out! I will do this...
只要满足以下条件
if the following conditions are met.
滚出我的房间
Get out of my fucking room!
首先  你同意永远结束
First, you agree to end the war on drugs,
毒品之战
once and for all.
所有级别的药物都合法化
All classes of substance are legalized...
为新市场铺路
paving the way to a new marketplace
在那里药品交易受到和酒精交易
in which sales are regulated and taxed...
一样的管理与税收
as per alcohol.
第二条  我的同事和我能获得司法豁免
And second, my colleagues and I receive full legal immunity.
达成我的条件
Meet my terms...
我就很愿意帮助你
and I look forward to helping you
继续捍卫我们亲爱国家的强大
keep our beloved country great...
促进我们失调的经济
boosting our ailing economy,
减轻执法部门的开销
and easing spending on law enforcement.
或者继续推行这种愚蠢的  过时的
Or continue this blinkered, outmoded...
实际上灾难性的禁令
and, frankly, disastrous exercise in prohibition...
让自己的双手沾满鲜血
and live with blood on your hands.
要想救人  就合法化
Save lives. Legalize.
我就说了那东西对你没好处
I told you that shit was no good for you.
罂粟·亚当斯是谁
Who is Poppy Adams?
新闻
快报
在哈佛商学院毕业后
After graduating Harvard Business School...
亚当斯曾短暂
Adams was briefly held
入院治疗严重的精神疾病
for serious mental health issues...
之后便消失得无影无踪
before disappearing without a trace.
聪明  野心勃勃  无情
Intelligent, ambitious, ruthless,
毫无同情心  浅薄
lacks empathy, superficial charm.
是成就伟大CEO的全部特质
All the elements of a great CEO.
也是精神病的全部特质
Or a psychopath.
在亚当斯给
Following the broadcast
总统的广播发言后
of Adams's message to the president...
今天在全国各地乃至世界各地的
there were scenes of chaos today...
医疗中心陷入了一片混乱
at medical centers across the country and around the world.
我们没有空病床了
We have no more beds available.
医院人满为患
The hospital is at full capacity.
蓝色皮疹现在被重新命名为
The blue rash is now being renamed.
舞者之疾
"The Dancing Disease"...
因为受害者开始出现第二阶段症状
as victims begin to exhibit stage two symptoms.
准备冷冻装置
Let's prep the cryo unit.
你想冷冻他吗
You want to freeze him?
正是
Exactly.
因受污染的娱乐性药物
Victims of the virus
感染该病毒的受害者们
caused by contaminated recreational drugs...
挤满了医院和诊所  为自己的性命担忧
flooded hospitals and clinics in fear for their lives.
宵禁和禁飞令
Curfews and no travel orders
在政府评估灾难规模后
are being considered as authorities assess
可能考虑实施
the scale of the disaster.
关上
Close it.
但总统并未
But there has still been
发表官方回应
no official response from the president...
他现在还在紧急商议中
who remains locked in emergency talks.
准备一份总统令
Prepare a presidential decree.
指示情报部门和执法人员暂停行动
Tell intelligence and law enforcement to stand down.
我们先配合这位女士
We're gonna dance to this lady's tune.
很好
Good.
我们可以解决的
We can make this work.
我们就说
We spin it that it's not a matter
不会和恐怖分子协商了
of negotiation with terrorists.
不  我的意思是
No, what I'm proposing...
假装同意她的要求
is we appear to agree to her demands
避免全球恐慌
to prevent global panic...
然后让那些瘾君子废物们自生自灭吧
and then let the junkie scum go down in flames. Huh?
对吧
Huh? Yeah.
把罂粟·亚当斯和她所谓的黄金圈一起拿下
Take Poppy Adams and her so-called Golden Circle down with them.
从此以后没人用毒品  没人交易毒品  这简直是双赢
No drug users, no drug trade. It's a win-win situation here.
但先生  受害者们并不在少数
But, sir, we're not talking about a handful of hostages.
世界各地的死亡规模
We could be looking at the deaths
可能达到数以百万计
of hundreds of millions worldwide.
数以百万计的罪犯
Hundreds of millions of criminals,
都是社会的累赘
burdens to society.
对吧  麦考伊
Am I right, McCoy?
没错  先生
Absolutely, sir.
但先生  这
But, sir, that's...
那些做实验的人怎么办
What about people who were just experimenting?
那些自我治疗的病人
Folks who self-medicate?
测药专家  甚至孩子呢
Functioning professionals? Kids?
别说教了  福克斯
Oh, spare me the crap, Fox.
事实是
The fact is,
这届总统在毒品之战上大获全胜
this presidency has just won the war on drugs.
恭喜您  总统先生
Congratulations, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
这值得我们干杯庆祝
And that deserves a toast.
这是缺乏职业道德  先生
This is totally unethical, sir.
联邦特工
肯塔基波旁威士忌酒
福克斯  给我闭嘴
Fox, shut up!
麦考伊  发布军事法
McCoy, declare martial law.
我们必须操控  征用体育场
We need to keep control, commandeer stadiums,
华盛顿DC
学校  师父大厦
schools, civic centers...
下令实施新闻管制
order a press blackout.
让军队待命
And put the military on standby
随时准备围剿瘾君子
to round these junkies up.
不管他们有没有破坏法律
Whether they broke the law or not,
这些受害人都是人类
those victims are human beings.
龙舌兰
Tequila.
可是个好家伙
He's a great guy.
也是个伟大的特工
And a great agent.
现在他被冷冻起来等待我们的帮助
Right now, he's lying in deep freeze waitin' on our help.
我们不能感情用事
We can't make this personal, sir.
感情用事
Personal?
特工  我们不能袖手旁观让他这样的人死去
Agent, we can't stand by and let folks like him die.
我们是他们唯一的希望了
These people, we're their only hope.
我们必须找到解药
Now, we have to find that antidote.
罂粟的存货可能在任何地方
Poppy's stockpiles, well, they could be anywhere.
她手里肯定有
She must have some on hand.
找到罂粟
Locate Poppy...
取一份样品拿来化验
and obtain a sample for analysis.
也许可以复制
Maybe it can be replicated.
很抱歉打断一下  伙计们
Sorry to cut in, guys.
但查理在和女友通电话
But Charlie is on the phone with his girlfriend.
将你们接入通话
Looping you in now.
别担心  我在用投币电话
Don't worry. I'm on a payphone...
全身都是蓝色皮疹
covered in a fucking blue rash.
为什么你没告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
你只是说  不要吃任何毒品
All you said was, "Don't take any drugs."
当时可是音乐节  行行好
It was a music festival for fuck's sake.
我靠  见鬼  见鬼  好吧
Fuck. Shit. Shit! Okay.
听着  你必须去意大利的实验室
Listen. You need to get to the lab in Italy.
你记得我们去哪里滑雪吗
Do you remember where we went skiing?
我记得
Yes. Yes, I remember.
在那里和我汇面
Yeah. Meet me there
我给你解药
and I'll give you the antidote.
好
Okay.
好了  飞机准备好了
All right. Jet's ready.
威士忌  加拉哈德去意大利
Whiskey, Galahad, get to Italy.
你们俩必须区分一下代号了
You two need to fix this code name thing.
恕我直言  先生
And with all due respect, sir...
我不认为老加拉哈德
I don't think Galahad senior
准备好执行任务了
is ready to return to fieldwork.
- 我确实说的是  - 当然
I did actually mean... Of course.
我无礼地说一下
And with all disrespect...
没有他我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere without him.
头脑  技术
Brains, skills...
跳绳
skipping rope?
- 是套索  - 随便
- It's a lasso. - Whatever.
来嘛
Come on.
去吧  去执行任务
Go on. Vamoose.
遵命
Yes, sir.
喝了它
Drink it.
已经开始见效了
It's working already.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
威士忌特工
Agent Whiskey.
目标地点证实有解药
Antidote confirmed at the target's location.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
等一下  我们需要你过来  加拉哈德
Hold up. We need you down here, Galahad.
看守控制室
To secure the control room.
也好  哈利
Probably a good idea, Harry.
在上面联系
Call you from the top, yeah?
你好
Buongiorno!
Buongiorno.
嘿
Hey!
很抱歉
So sorry about this.
进入控制室  已就位
At the controls. In position.
让缆车停在这等我们回来
Keep this cable car here till we get back.
收到  艾格西
Roger that, Eggsy.
克拉拉绝对在这
Clara's definitely here.
接近了
We're getting warmer.
哈利·哈特  哈利·哈特  超级间谍  超级间谍
Harry Hart, Harry Hart, super spy, super spy.
似乎碰到了一扇门
Looks like we've got a door.
是的
Yep.
好了
There you go.
我掩护
I'll cover.
你好啊
Hi, there.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
你们这里真难找
You guys did not make this place easy to find.
你谁啊
Who are you?
我是来收解药的
I'm here to collect this antidote.
送去新加坡吗
For Singapore?
是
Yeah.
你是吴霆锋吗
You are Wu Ting Feng?
是的
Yes.
你怎么还活着
Hey, how are you still alive?
小河  你在这做什么呢
River, what are you doing here?
小河
River?
你好啊  克拉拉
Hi, Clara.
发生在格拉斯托的事情  就留在格拉斯托吧
What happens at Glasto, stays in Glasto.
- 你个混蛋  - 再见  查理
You motherfucker! Bye, Charlie.
拉响警报
Sound the alarm!
你这个小偷
You fucking cockroach!
关上门  给
Jam the door! Give...
见鬼
Fuck!
加拉哈德我们来了
Galahad, we're coming.
下面安全吗
All clear at the bottom?
加拉哈德  回话
Galahad, come in!
- 给我打开门  - 他们被锁住了
- Open the fucking door. - They've locked.
打开门
Open the door!
哈利  快点  我们进去了  我们该走了
Harry, come on, we're in. Let's go.
闪开  蝴蝶们
Away, butterflies.
蝴蝶  不  哈利  你得把门给我们关上  拜托
Butterfly? No, Harry. You've got to shut the doors, please.
快点  我们得撤了  拜托
Come on. We've gotta go now. Please!
把门关上  哈利
Shut the fucking door, Harry!
哈利  你在吗
Harry, are you there?
干得漂亮  哈利  很好  谢谢
Well done, Harry. Good. Thanks, man.
快点
Come on. Now!
大门解锁
- 完成了  - 谢谢
- It's done. - Thank you.
下面情况还好吗  哈利
You all good down there, Harry?
没有问题
All clear.
你好  艾格西
Hello, Eggsy.
祝你旅途愉快  哥们
Enjoy the ride, bruv.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
所有按键都失效了  控制台失控了
All the buttons are dead. Controls gone.
系统覆写
控制系统都被关闭了  艾格西  靠你自己了
Everything's in shutdown. You're on your own, Eggsy.
那是什么玩意
What the fuck is that?
天啊
Oh, my God.
你一定是在开玩笑
You've gotta be fucking kidding!
我了个大槽  那到底怎么回事
Jesus fucking Christ! What the fuck is that?
什么情况
What the hell is that?
我靠
Shit!
这是三周来我拉的最多的一回
That's the first decent shit I've had in three weeks.
哈利  在紧急汇合点见面
Harry, meet us at the emergency rendezvous point.
收到
Roger that.
获得你的方位了
Got you on the GPS.
想想这么小的东西能拯救世界
So weird to think this tiny thing
就感觉很奇怪
could save the world.
让我看看
Let me have a look.
哈利
Harry.
我来晚了吗
Am I late?
你们拿到解药了
You found the antidote.
趴下
Get down!
你个混蛋
You fucking dickhead!
去你的  我刚救了你的命
Fuck you! I just saved your life!
那是以数百万人性命为代价的
Yeah, and cost millions of people theirs!
他们在找掩护  填充弹药
All right, they're going for cover and reloading.
我要去教训他们  掩护我  兄弟们
I'll fix their wagons. Cover me, boys!
等等
Wait.
艾格西  他可能是敌方的间谍
Eggsy, I think he could be working for the other side.
你有什么毛病
What the fuck is wrong with you?
你是脑卡了  快看
You're having a brain fart! Look!
他看着像他们的同伙吗
Does that look like he's working with them?
哈利  你又看到蝴蝶了吗
Harry, are you seeing butterflies again?
我知道自己看到了什么
I know what I'm seeing.
他都不需要我们帮忙  干得漂亮
Good job he didn't need our help.
谢天谢地我不需要后援
Thank fucking Christ I didn't need any backup!
我没子弹了  运兵车来了
I'm out of ammo! Troop carrier coming in.
你们有什么
What've you got?
见鬼
Fuck!
我靠  他们有一堆人
Shit! There's a fuck ton of 'em!
这是啥
What is this?
你的行李好像是为睡衣晚会准备的  不是执行任务用的
Looks like you packed for a fucking slumber party, not a mission!
他们居然有加特林机枪
And they've got fucking Gatling guns!
给你们十秒投降否则我们就开火了
You have 10 seconds to surrender before we open fire!
兄弟们  快点决定
Guys, hurry up!
10!
喂
Hey!
- 9  - 蝴蝶男
- 9! - Butterfly guy!
8!
你看起来好像没被金杰治好
You don't look like Ginger fixed you right.
7!
我说了我没子弹了
I said I'm empty!
- 6  - 把你的给我
- 6! - Give me yours.
5!
哈利  把枪给他
Harry, give him the fucking gun!
4!
哈利  不要
Harry, no!
不管了  开火吧
Oh, fuck it! Fire!
哈利  蹲下
Harry, get down!
说真的  哈利
I mean, honestly, Harry,
你到底有什么毛病
what the fuck is wrong with you?
他是故意弄掉药瓶的
He broke the vial on purpose!
你是个大蠢蛋  疯掉了吧  哈利
You're a fucking idiot! You're out of control, Harry!
如果我们逃离这里  他会把我们杀死的
If we made it out of here, he was gonna kill us both!
真该死  看起来用不着他来杀我们了
For fuck's sake, it looks like he wouldn't have fucking had to!
真是没信心
Oh, ye of little faith.
即使如此  也不能弥补你犯的错
This does not mean you're off the fucking hook!
我们得藏起来
We need to go dark.
我们不知道联邦特工中
We don't know who else at Statesman
谁还是我们的敌人
could be working against us.
见鬼  这是我的错
Shit! This is all my fault.
你就没准备好执行任务
You weren't ready for the field
我却坚持让你来
and I pushed for it!
他展露了自己的目的
He showed his hand.
你觉得他会让我们活下去吗
You think he'd have let us live?
你应该感谢我解决了我们的麻烦
You should be thanking me for saving our arses!
解决了我们的麻烦
Saving our arses?
这话你跟威士忌说吧
Try saying that to fucking Whiskey!
你真是不可理喻
You are unbelievable!
- 梅林  能听到吗  - 能  艾格西
- Merlin, can you hear me? - Yes, Eggsy.
威士忌倒下了  中弹了
Whiskey's down. He's been shot.
发生什么了
What happened?
他在交火中受伤了
He got caught in the crossfire.
我给他使用了阿尔法胶  我们会带他回去
I've applied the alpha gel. We'll bring him in.
但首先  我必须想办法回到实验室
But first, I've gotta find a way to get back up to that lab
拿到更多解药
and retrieve more antidote.
查理  发生了什么  你在哪
Charlie, what's happening? Where are you?
一切尽在掌控之中
Everything's under control.
很抱歉查理  真的很抱歉
I'm sorry, Charlie. I'm so sorry.
请别告诉罂粟他们是跟踪我找到的
Please don't tell Poppy it was me they followed.
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, darling.
发生在意大利的事
What happens in Italy...
就留在意大利吧
stays in Italy.
谢谢
Thank you.
梅林  改变计划  吴霆锋  新加坡
Merlin, change of plans. Wu Ting Feng, Singapore.
- 谁  - 就是这个意思
- Who? - Exactly.
那是我们唯一的线索了
It's the only lead we've got.
那你最好找出他是谁
So I suggest you find out who he is.
来吧
Come on.
律师助理
吴霆锋  他是律师事务所的律师助理
Wu Ting Feng, he's an assistant at a law firm.
穿过他们的防火墙
Let's get through their firewall.
好的
Yep.
梅林
Merlin...
除了这个之外你有想要过别的吗
have you ever wanted to do more than this?
- 你是认真的吗  - 是的
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
这工作很重要
This is vital.
没有我们  他们就输了
Without us, they'd be lost.
我知道  但你知道我是什么意思
I know, but you know what I mean.
去执行任务
Get out there in the field.
你有申请过吗
Well, have you ever asked?
当然有
Of course I have.
但每次特工的职位空缺
But every time an agent's position has come up...
威士忌都投票反对我
Whiskey has voted against me.
- 不是吧  - 是的
- No. - Yeah.
等一下  快看这个
Wait, wait, wait. Look, check it out.
罂粟发来的邮件
Email in from Poppy,
是发给那个律所的高级合伙人的
from a senior partner at the firm.
是坐标
They're coordinates.
柬埔寨
Cambodia?
你在亚洲有侦查无人机吗
You have any reconnaissance drones down in Asia?
当然有  现在就派过去
Sure do. Sending them in right now.
政府今天要求
The government today urged.
黄金圈受害者
Golden Circle victims...
到全国各地建立的临时
to report to the temporary field hospitals
医院报道
now set up across the country.
总统处理危机的办法
The president's handling of the crisis
“舞蹈病”威胁世界
突发新闻
被世界其他领导人赞扬
has been commended by other world leaders.
我靠  政治从来没有这么简单
Damn. Politics has never been so easy.
天啊  福克斯
Oh, Jesus, Fox.
怎么了
What?
天
Oh, God.
我说过了  先生
Like I said, sir...
这病毒影响了各种背景的人
this affects all people from all backgrounds.
我对你很失望  福克斯
I'm disappointed, Fox.
失望且恶心
Disappointed and disgusted.
总统先生  我每天20小时
Mr. President, I routinely work
为您卖命  没有一天休息
a 20 hour day for you, 7 days a week.
也许有些人不需要吃药就能做到
Maybe some can do that without chemical help.
无数的人将会死去
Countless people are going to die.
你可以拯救他们的  先生
You can save them, sir.
像我一样无辜的人
Innocent people like me.
没那么无辜
Not that innocent.
他的状态很好
He looks great.
很好
Good.
好消息  先生们
Good news, gentlemen.
很快他就能恢复了
He'll be back on his feet in no time.
我不认为这是好主意
I'm not certain that's a good idea.
那是什么意思
What do you mean?
我朝威士忌特工开的枪  有意为之
I shot Agent Whiskey. Deliberately.
什么  为什么
What, why?
他在为敌人效力
He was working against us.
在我们找出原因之前  我觉得还是谁都不要相信
And until we find out why, I say we trust no one.
梅林  哈利生病了
Merlin, Harry's sick.
整件事都是我的错
This whole thing is my fault.
我以为他准备好了
I thought he was ready.
蒂尔德
很抱歉  我得接个电话
I'm sorry, I've got to take this.
听我说
Listen to me.
这和我的心理健康无关
This is not about my mental health.
如果我们之间有个双重间谍
If there's a chance there's a double agent in our midst...
或者更严重  这是联邦特工自己的秘密日程
or worse, if Statesman itself has a dark agenda...
我们必须保护好这次行动
we have to safeguard this mission.
我们都知道总统希望受害者们死
We both know the president wants these victims dead.
宝贝
Hey, baby.
嘿
Hey.
我靠
Fuck.
哈利  我相信你  一直都相信你
Look, Harry, I trust you. I always have.
但情况是  我们需要联邦特工的资源
But it's about this situation. We need Statesman's resources.
我需要知道你是否适合执行任务
And I need to know that you are fit for work.
宝贝  为什么你没个我打电话
Babe, why didn't you call me?
你是香蕉人吗
Are you the banana man?
听着  我们很快就会
Listen, we're on the verge of finding
找到解药了  会没事的
an antidote. It's gonna be all right.
向左看一下
Now, look left for me.
我的大脑没毛病
There's nothing wrong with my brain.
向右看
Look right.
你在国防部发现
Can you remember the headline
间谍网的时候新闻头条是什么吗
when you uncovered that spy ring in the Pentagon?
和足球有关  英国以5比1击败德国
The football. England beat Germany, 5-1.
对撒切尔的刺杀企图呢
Thatcher's assassination attempt.
查理和戴妃的婚礼
Charles and Di's wedding.
嘿  比约恩博格
Hey, Bjorn Borg.
宝贝  如果你能听到我
Babe, if you can hear me,
我希望你知道我爱你
I want you to know that I love you.
如果我们度过难关  我安全回来了
And if we get through this, and you'll have me back...
不论如何  我都想和你在一起
I wanna be with you. No matter what.
我保证不会让你失望
I promise I won't let you down.
会没事的
It's all gonna be all right.
我最爱的歌手
My favorite singer.
我根本不知道  我怎么可能知道呢
I don't bloody know. How would I know that?
- 是约翰·丹佛  - 梅林
- It's John Denver. - Merlin!
你得到那个地方的监控没有
Have you got eyes on that location yet?
快了  无人侦察机还有一小时到
Soon. The reconnaissance drone's about an hour away.
这样我们就有时间解决
Which gives us time to sort out...
胡扯  我们什么时间都没有
Bollocks, we haven't time for anything.
我现在走了  不管你来不来
I'm leaving now. With or without you.
你好
Hello!
表明自己的身份
Identify yourself.
我叫斯泰西·普鲁伊特  我是罂粟·亚当斯的律师
My name is Stacey Prewitt. I'm Ms. Poppy Adams' attorney.
罂粟  今晚你要见律师吗
Poppy, you expecting a lawyer tonight?
是的  请放他进来
Oh, yes. Please send him in.
但别忘记之后重新开启地雷
But don't forget to reactivate the landmines.
晚上好  亚当斯女士
Good evening, Ms. Adams.
我的律师现在就把文件带过去
My lawyer is bringing you the document right now.
快点
Hurry up.
你在你联署后
And once you countersign,
就会变成行政法令
it becomes an executive decree...
你不能反悔
and you can't back out,
然后我就放出解药
and then I release the antidote.
你能向我保证
Can you give me any assurance
按时发放解药吗
you can get it out there in time?
从哪里发放呢
And where's it gonna come from?
花多久才能分出去
How long it'll take to distribute?
这你不用担心  我有严密监管的存货
I wouldn't worry about that. I have secure stockpiles...
在世界上所有大城市里藏着
hidden in every major city worldwide.
当我输入密码
And when I enter the access code...
我的无人机大军
my fleet of drones
就会立即发放解药
will distribute the antidote immediately.
所以别浪费时间  签文件吧
So don't dilly-dally signin' that document
时间不等人
'cause time is running out.
你个蠢婊子
You dumb bitch!
你还好吗
You all right?
谁给你打的电话
What was that phone call you got?
别说了  哈利
Let's not, Harry.
你应该不会可怜我
I don't think you'd sympathize...
我现在也不想听说教
and I'm not really in the mood for a lecture.
好吧
All right.
喝马提尼吗  念在旧时的份上
How about a martini? For old times' sake?
好吧
Yeah, all right.
我有个女友
I had a girlfriend.
我失去了她
I lost her.
我很心碎
And it broke me.
如果这个任务失败
And now, if this mission fails...
她会死的
she's gonna die.
我知道这违反了王牌特工的规矩
I know it's against Kingsman rules,
谈恋爱
having a relationship.
当我被枪打中
When I was shot...
你能猜到我脑中浮现的
can you guess what the last thing was
最后一件事是什么吗
that flashed through my mind?
什么事都没有
It was absolutely nothing.
我没有亲密的人
I had no ties.
没有苦乐参半的回忆
No bittersweet memories.
我并没有抛弃什么
I was leaving nothing behind.
从未有过伴侣
Never experienced companionship...
从未坠入过爱河
never been in love...
那时候
and in that moment...
我只感到了孤独
all I felt was loneliness...
和后悔
and regret.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
不需要
Don't be.
你要知道心理有担心的事
Just know that having something to lose...
才让人活着值
is what makes life worth living.
现在我们去救你的女友吧
Now, let's go and save your girl.
我想你了  哈利
I missed you, Harry.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我不想打断你们的派对
I hate to break up a party.
我们快到了  所以我们开始准备吧
We're nearly there, so I suggest we get ready.
跟我来
Follow me.
太棒了
Oh, yes.
你好啊  美女
Hello, gorgeous.
我叫杰克  你叫什么
I'm Jack. What's your name?
你想不想坐着正宗牛仔回家啊
How would you like to ride home on a real cowboy?
我有半打冰啤酒
I got a six pack of cold ones on ice
室友晚上也不回家
and my roomie's out all night.
到时候你可以尽可能大声喊我的名字  甜心
So you can scream my name as loud as you need to, sugar.
我也不想这样对你  杰克
I hate to do this to you, Jack.
这位美女是谁
Who's this pretty lady?
她死了
She's dead.
警察说是误杀
Cops said wrong place, wrong time.
亲爱的  我要去趟杂货店
Hey, honey. I'm heading to the grocery store.
我叫罂粟·亚当斯
My name is Poppy Adams.
金杰
Ginger.
那个蝴蝶男开抢打了我的脑袋
Goddamn butterfly guy shot me in the fucking head.
为什么
Why would he do that?
估计是你没治好他
Well, I'm guessing you didn't fix him right.
他现在在哪呢
And where the hell is he?
他在和艾格西还有梅林去柬埔寨的路上
He's on his way to Cambodia with Eggsy and Merlin.
罂粟的大本营就在那
That's where Poppy's base is.
艾格西会需要有人支援
Eggsy's gonna need backup.
是的
Yes, he is.
帮我把银色小马弄到跑道上
Get the Silver Pony on the runway
准备出发
and ready to take off.
嘿嘿
Hey, hey.
很精神呐  梅林
Looking good, Merlin.
感觉也很棒  艾格西
Feeling good, Eggsy.
对了  这是你的
Right. This is yours.
这是给你的
That's for you.
按S
Press the "S".
扫雷棒
Minesweeper.
联邦特工的礼物
Courtesy of Statesman.
- 这是什么  - 小心
- And what about these? - Careful.
它们是手雷
Those are hand grenades.
如之前约好的
As discussed...
这在最后时刻用
this is for the endgame.
我把它交给你了
I'm entrusting it to you.
而这个
And I'm entrusting this...
交给我
to me.
银色★小马驹
威士忌
全世界成千上万的黄金圈受害者
Millions of Golden Circle victims worldwide...
现在正进入第三阶段  麻痹
are now entering stage three paralysis.
在最近的声明中
In his latest statement...
总统承诺会
the president promised he was doing
动用所有权力来
everything in his power...
加快谈判进程  拯救生命
to speed up negotiations and save lives.
但惊恐的声音越来越多
But fears are growing that for many,
再晚些就来不及了
it may soon be too late.
我们的心和祷告与受害者同在
Our thoughts and prayers are with the victims.
上帝保佑我们
God help us all.
罂粟国度
好了  我们在这分头行动
Right. This is where we split up.
两面夹击
Pincer movement.
梅林  你和我一起
Merlin, you're with me.
艾格西  我们就位后看你信号
Eggsy, you signal when we're in position.
别动
Don't move.
你动了  我们就得死
You move, we die.
幸亏  我们有这个
Luckily, I have this.
这个喷雾能把触发器冻住
This spray will freeze the trigger mechanism...
能让我们有短暂的时间离开
give us a split second.
我数到三
So on the count of three...
我让你
what I want you to...
梅林
Merlin!
梅林  您老干了啥
Merlin, what the fuck have you done?
我们好几年前就一起并肩战斗
Our journey together began many years ago...
当时你的父亲为我们做了同样的事情
when your father did the same thing for us.
我们的经历开始于我犯的一个错误
Our journey began with a mistake I made.
把你手里的罐给我  这是命令
Give me the can. That's an order.
罐空了
Can's empty.
这短短的几秒钟也到头了
Split second's over.
你俩得继续未完的事
You two need to get going.
不不不  一定有其他的解决办法的
No, no, no. There's got to be another way.
他说的对
He's right.
任务是第一位的
Mission comes first.
任务是第一位个屁
Bollocks, mission comes first!
艾格西
Eggsy!
没时间跟你兄弟情深  记住你做过的训练
This is no time for emotion. Remember your training.
否则我们就都狗带了
Or we all die.
赶紧给我去继续
Now get on with it.
按照命令做  快去
Do as you're told. Move it!
去吧
Go.
跟你并肩作战很荣幸
It's been an honor.
祝你好运
Good luck.
♪ 西弗吉尼亚 ♪
♪ Almost heaven ♪
BGM:Take Me Home, Country Road - John Denver（已故）
♪ 宛如天堂 ♪
♪ West Virginia ♪
♪ 蓝岭山高 ♪
♪ Blue Ridge Mountains ♪
♪ 谢兰多河水流淌 ♪
♪ Shenandoah River ♪
- 罂粟  请回复  - 收到
- Poppy, come in. - Roger.
♪ 生命长久 ♪
♪ Life is old there ♪
你是想再要个律师吗
Are you expecting another lawyer?
♪ 久于树木♪
♪ Older than the trees ♪
有个人在这唱歌
There's a guy here singing.
♪ 长于山川 ♪
♪ Younger than the mountains ♪
唱歌
Singing?
♪ 好似清风拂面 ♪
♪ Blowin' like a breeze ♪
♪ 乡间小路 ♪
♪ Country roads ♪
♪ 带我回家 ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ 带我回到那 ♪
♪ To the place ♪
♪ 属于我的地方 ♪
♪ I belong ♪
把他带过来
Bring him to me.
♪ 西弗吉尼亚 ♪
♪ West Virginia ♪
♪ 高山妈妈 ♪
♪ Mountain momma ♪
♪ 乡间小路 ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ 带我回家 ♪
♪ Country road ♪
罂粟  我们这有情况
Poppy, we got a situation here.
♪ 乡间小路 ♪
♪ Country roads ♪
♪ 带我回家 ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ 带我回到  魂牵梦绕的地方♪
♪ To the place I belong ♪
♪ 西弗吉尼亚 ♪
♪ West Virginia ♪
♪ 高山妈妈 ♪
♪ Mountain momma ♪
♪ 乡间小路 ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ 带我回家 ♪
♪ Country roads ♪
他站在了一个地雷上
He stepped on a land mine.
哪个人过去清理一下
Can we get somebody out there to clean that up?
有人吗
Hello?
糟了  我们被攻击了
Crap. We're under attack.
袭击警报  袭击警报
Code five. Code five.
你俩  赶紧给我起来
You two, off your fuckin' asses.
去守门
Guard the door.
埃尔顿爵士  待在这  我们被袭击了
Sir Elton, stay here. We're under attack.
Sir. Elton
英国滚石乐队摇滚歌手埃尔顿·约翰
著名同性恋
- 是有人来救援了吗  - 也许是
- Is it a rescue attempt? - Might be.
太好了
Yes!
♪ 周三  周三 ♪
♪ Wednesday, Wednesday ♪
BGM:Saturday Night's Alright(For Fighting) - Sir. John Elton
♪ 周三  周三 ♪
♪ Wednesday, Wednesday ♪
♪ 周三夜晚没问题 ♪
♪ Wednesday night's alright ♪
♪ 嘿 ♪
♪ Hey ♪
难道不应该是周六吗
Isn't that supposed to be Saturday?
- 今天周几  - 周三
- What day is it today? - Wednesday.
没错
Exactly!
- 埃尔顿  你给我冷静  - 我日
- Elton, just calm down. - Fuck you!
别动  埃尔顿
Stay there, Elton.
滚
Fuck off!
要不然我就日了你
Or I'll fuck you up.
我日
Fuck me.
卧槽  把这个带走  快点
Holy cow. Get this out of here. Go!
艾格西  去拿箱子
Eggsy, get the case.
你得告诉我
You are going to tell me...
接入密码是多少
what the access code is.
加油  杰特  好孩子
Come on, Jet. Good girl.
日你大爷
Motherfucker!
埃尔顿·约翰
友方
别挡路  埃尔顿
Get out of the way, Elton.
后退  它被设定不能伤害我
Stay down. It's not allowed to hurt me.
谢谢您了
Thank you.
手臂入侵
程序校正
日你  罂粟
Fuck you, Poppy!
日你大爷  埃尔顿
Fuck you, Elton.
杀了埃尔顿·约翰
Kill Elton John.
我日
Fuck!
埃尔顿  拿着球
Elton, take the ball.
谢谢合作
Thank you.
现在  你走吧  去拯救世界
Now, go off and save the world.
如果我去拯救世界  能给我来两张
If I save the world, can I have two tickets
你下一场演唱会的门票不
to your next concert?
亲爱的  如果你救了世界
Darling, if you save the world,
你可以直通后台
you can have a backstage pass.
我日你大爷
Fuck you.
到点了  不跟你玩了
Time's up.
我日
Fuck!
贝妮  贝妮  贝妮
Bennie, Bennie, Bennie!
去追他们
Get them!
完美解决
Got it.
杀了他  贝妮
Kill him, Bennie!
这呢  跟上  好孩子
Here, heel! Heel! Good boy!
来这里
Come on!
把密码给我
Give me the code.
不  我们还没完事呢
No. We're not done yet.
你真幸运  查理
Lucky for you, Charlie...
我们其中有一个人明白
one of us understands
绅士的真正含义
what it means to be a gentleman.
我们公平点
Let's make this fair.
给我密码
Give me the code!
我不能
I can't.
因为只有罂粟知道
Only Poppy knows it.
好吧  那你就对我没用了  对吧
Well, then you're no use to me, are you?
郑重声明  查理
For the record, Charlie...
我确实比你绅士多了
I'm more of a gentleman than you'll ever be.
但现在  是时候稍稍不那么绅士了
But right now, it's time to drop the gentle bit.
为了王牌特工
This is for Kingsman.
为了我的伙伴布兰登
For my mate Brandon.
为了罗克茜
For Roxy.
为了JB
For JB.
也为了梅林
And for Merlin.
睡个好觉  兄弟
Good night, bruv.
罂粟餐厅
嘿  小伙们
Hey, fellas.
你给我们密码
You're going to give us the code.
我要是不呢
Or what?
因为你看起来不像那种会
'Cause you don't seem like the kind of gentleman
伤害女士的绅士
who would hurt a lady.
也许吧  可以说我很老派
Perhaps not. Call me old-fashioned...
我认为毁灭人类特别不是女士的作风
I don't consider genocide especially ladylike.
好了  闲聊够了吧
Right. Enough small talk.
密码给我们
Give us the code.
好啊
Sure.
不  我不想给
No. I don't think so.
海洛因
Heroin.
你知道吗  在我家乡
You know, where I come from...
你卖的这个玩意  毁了好多条命
this shit you've been peddling's ruined a lot of lives.
但给你的这支更狠
But yours is even more deadly.
但这药感觉太好了  能让你
But it feels so nice, it's gonna make you
降低警惕
lower your guard.
我们的同事  梅林  希望他的在天之灵
Our colleague, Merlin, may he rest in peace...
能合成你那可怕的配方
managed to synthesize your horrible little formula...
加快药效
and speed up its effects.
我估计你在开始麻痹和停止呼吸之前
So I would say you have just under eight minutes...
还有不到8分钟
before paralysis sets in and your breathing stops.
但  当然  你非常了解这个药
But, of course, you know all about that.
所以我们来做个交易  你在全世界范围内释放解药
So here's the deal. You release the antidote worldwide,
我们就能让你获得解药
and we make sure you get a dose.
我得给你密码才能活
I have to give you the code to live?
亲爱的  你真是太聪明了  你应该为我工作的
Honey, you're so smart. You should work for me.
没错  把密码给我们
Right. Give us the code.
为什么不呢  法令马上要颁布了
Why not? The decree's getting signed soon...
所有人  呃
anyhoo. Um...
密码是  素食之恋
It's "Viva las vegan."
懂吗
Get it?
拉斯维加斯之恋
"Viva las..."
来陪陪我
Come snuggle with me.
我喜欢你
I like you.
应该不太可能
I don't think that's terribly likely.
她吸毒过量了
She's OD'd.
你给她注射太多了
You gave her too much.
是吗
Did I?
你知道的  我与毒品的经历
You know, I really don't have as much experience with all this drug stuff...
没有大家认为的那么多
as people think.
希望密码是真的
Better be the right code.
素食之恋
"Viva las..."
怎么样
So?
别动  孩子
Don't move, kid.
如果你玩把戏
You try anything funny,
我就把这绳子通电
and I'll turn this thing electric.
现在放下你的枪  小伙  把它们滑过来
Now give up your guns, fellas. Slide 'em over.
威士忌
Whiskey.
我们是一伙的
We are all on the same side here.
你脑袋曾经受过伤
You've had a head injury.
哈利也发生过一样的事
The exact same thing happened to Harry.
你们都有同样的脑部小毛病
You're havin' some sort of brain glitch.
不  我的脑袋好着呢  孩子
Nope. My brain's all good, kid.
你知道吗
And you know what?
我猜你这个朋友哈利也是一样  脑袋没毛病
I reckon the same was true for your friend Harry over here.
直觉很准呢  不得不夸夸
Real fine instincts, I'll give him that.
待着别动
So stay still...
否则我就把他切成特别小的小块
or I'll dice him up so small,
让你把他装进桶里带回家
you can take him home in a bucket...
还能有地方放你兄弟  梅林
and still have room for what's left
剩下的骸骨
of your buddy, Merlin.
好吧  那真他妈是太好了
Well, that's just fucking great.
你是给总统干活的吗
You're working for the president?
那个混蛋
That asshole?
当然不是  这是个人原则问题  特工
Hell no. It's a matter of personal principle, agent.
不再有嗑药的
No more drug users.
那么联邦英雄酿酒厂的股票价格就能上去了
And the Statesman share price rockets.
所以这就是你的原则  赚钱
So those are your principles? Making money?
我们建立特工组织是为了维持和平的
Our agencies were founded to uphold peace.
为了保护无辜的人
To protect the innocent.
你想知道谁是无辜的吗
Do you wanna know who was innocent?
我高中时的恋人
My high school sweetheart.
我一生的挚爱
Love of my life.
怀了我们的儿子
Pregnant with my little boy.
如果他妈妈没有卷入
He'd be about your age now...
两个冰毒头子为了
if his mama hadn't got caught in the crossfire...
抢劫一个便利店的交火中
when two meth head freaks
他大概有你这么大了
decided to rob a fucking convenience store.
如果世界没有那帮人
A world without those people in it...
那对我来说才确实是和平的
sure smells like peace to me.
你违反了法律
You break the law...
那你就要付出代价
you pay the price.
对他们来说
Good riddance...
是一种解脱
to all of them.
这就是为什么我准备毁了这个箱子
That's why I got to destroy that case.
现在把它滑过来  加拉哈德特工
Now slide it over, Agent Galahad.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道吗  哈利
Do you know what, Harry?
我觉着他给我提了个醒
I think he's got a point.
听起来是个好主意
I think it sounds like a bright idea.
给这堆东西喷上阿尔法凝胶  真是个傻逼
Put alpha gel on that, dickhead.
素食之恋
"Viva las vegan."
敬你  梅林
This one's for you, Merlin.
释放解药
这是个全球欢庆的日子
It's a day of worldwide celebration
释放解药：成千上万人获救
福克斯新闻快报
数百万人
as millions rejoice...
在他们或他们爱的人获救之后互相庆祝
after they or their loved ones were saved from death.
黄金圈解药持续分配到各处
Distribution of The Golden Circle antidote continues...
战地医院正在清空患者
and field hospitals are emptying...
受害者们今晚都会被治愈后回到家
as victims return to their homes tonight, cured.
加油  利亚姆  兄弟
Come on, Liam. Man, come on.
太好了  太好了
Yes! Yes! Yes!
我爱死你了  兄弟  我爱死你了
I love you, man! I love you!
我再也不会碰那玩意了
I'm never touching that shit again!
发生什么了
What happened?
- 我错过什么了吗  - 当然
- Did I miss something? - You sure did.
现在开始  龙舌兰特工  我建议你光喝酒
From now on, Tequila, I suggest you stick to booze.
总统因批准
The president actively sanctioned
成百上千民众死亡
the deaths of hundreds of millions of people...
欺骗了公众
and lied to the public.
我很荣幸负责对他的弹劾
I am proud to be responsible for his impeachment...
总统被弹劾
福克斯新闻快报
我将会尽我所能
and I will do everything I can
确保权力顺利交接
to ensure a smooth transition of power.
为了纪念这历史性的时刻
In honor of this historic occasion,
我们在苏格兰
we have purchased...
买了一个酿酒厂
a distillery in Scotland.
这向世界表示
This shows the world...
我们王牌特工也参与酿酒事业了
that Kingsman is now joining the liquor business.
之前我们是堂兄弟
Before we were cousins.
现在我们是亲兄弟  肩并肩一起工作
Now we're brothers, working side-by-side.
我们的资源现在也是你们的
All our resources are now yours.
你们可以借此重建了
You can rebuild.
是的  你们现在肯定激动屎了
Yeah, y'all shittin' in high cotton now.
龙舌兰特工  这就是正式的场合
Agent Tequila, this is a formal occasion...
你的领带和夹克呢
where's your tie and jacket?
对不起  先生
Sorry, sir.
希望王牌特工的兄弟们能给你打扮得合体些
Maybe the Kingsman boys can dress you properly.
敬我们的联盟
To our union!
最后一个命令
Final order of business...
如果你们中的某人
we would be honored
成为我们新的威士忌特工  我们会感到荣幸的
if one of you would be our new Agent Whiskey.
是的  这两个加拉哈德是在太让人迷糊了
Yeah, this two Galahad thing is just fucking confusing.
当然  我十分荣幸
Well, I'm very honored...
老大
Champ...
我想加入
I'd like to throw my hat in the ring.
好的
All right!
特工们  投票吧
Statesmen, the vote.
看起来她入选了
Looks like she's in.
请坐吧
Have a seat.
敬威士忌特工
To Agent Whiskey!
Agent Whiskey!
干杯
Cheers!
你确定我看起来不像傻逼吗
Are you sure I don't look like a dick?
自己照照镜子
Look in the mirror.
你看到什么了
What do you see?
一个完全不相信发生了什么  一脸懵逼的人
Someone who can't believe what the fuck is going on.
我看到了一个可敬的
I see a man who is honorable...
勇敢的
brave...
忠诚的
loyal...
发挥了他巨大潜力的人
who's fulfilled his huge potential.
一个一生里做了些有意义的事的人
A man who's done something good with his life.
一切都是你给的  哈利
I owe you everything, Harry.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Don't mention it.
准备好了吗
You ready?
毫无疑问
Not a doubt in my mind.
就像我们曾经王牌特工创始人说过的一样
As one of our founding Kingsman once said...
这不是终结
this is not the end.
甚至都不是终结的开始
It is not even the beginning of the end.
但  可能是  开始的终结
But it is, perhaps, the end of the beginning.
太好了
Yeah!